Oh no.
Welcome Living Mana Church family. It's
so good to have you here with us. I feel
like I was just here like maybe 12 hours
ago, which I was. We were doing some um
some programming last night, but we are
happy that you are here with us today.
Please continue. I have to say continue
to put in the chat where you're viewing
from and then put a one if this is your
very first time visiting with Living
Mana Church. We want to tell you a
little bit about who we are and
hopefully you will be so blessed that
you'll want to come back and worship
with us again. So again, please put in
the chat where you're viewing from. I
know you guys have been on here. We
started a little late today. So, I'm
going to go through and see who has
already put in the chat where you're
viewing from and ah I don't see I see a
lot of you guys are talking and
conversating which is great. Love to see
the fellowship with Living Mana Church.
I don't see a lot of locations. So,
please let me know. I know you guys are
somewhere so just let us know where you
are so we can say a special uh welcome
to you. So, Veronica, welcome. and
you're coming from Washington State, the
beautiful state of Washington. Uh we
have the UK here. I'm sorry the name
went up faster, but I saw the UK. We
have Christie from South Carolina. Good
to see you here. Uh let us know if you
guys were here last night when it wasn't
for Living Matter Church. It was for
Power of the Lamb live event, but we did
the third three third part series of the
T horns. Let us know if you were there
for that and you're here. Welcome again
from Wuhan, China. You have been
worshiping with us uh lately. You were
here last week. Good to see you here. We
have Rose from New York. Great to see
you here. We're happy to have all of you
here. Um we have British Columbia,
Canada. Welcome. Have Zambia. Welcome.
Good to see you. Love to see all the
different countries and of course the
states here in the United States. But we
are an international online church and
we just love to see so many um different
countries and places. I saw Kenya just
went up, New Jersey, France. Guys, we
are worldwide today.
>> We got all these continents going on and
all over the place. Let's see. Um we
have Canada.
Yeah, good to see you guys. Welcome.
>> Amen.
>> Amen. It's good to have an international
church. get to fellowship with people
from all around the world. It is truly a
blessing to have you here and we are
thrilled to have you.
>> Yeah.
>> San Jose, California where we came from.
>> Right next door, next little town over
uh Ethiopia. I have to say you're not a
one Ethiopia. I don't think I've ever
said welcome from someone to Ethiopia.
So, if this is your first time the
person from Ethiopia, please put a one.
Welcome. So good to have you. Uh,
Northern California, welcome, welcome,
welcome, welcome to all of our viewing
audience. Wow, that's great. I'd love to
know if Ethiopia is a one because I
don't I don't know. In four years, you
could forget. It's almost four years. I
shouldn't claim four years. Almost four
years, but I don't remember saying a
welcome to someone from Ethiopia. So,
that's great. Oh, wait. Somebody from
Pine Forge. Welcome.
my high school I graduated from.
Do I know this person from Pine Forge?
Is this my dear friend? It went up so
fast. Okay,
>> there it is. Right there.
>> Yes, it is. Andrea Young, yes. I thought
it was you. Welcome. Good to see you. We
have to talk. I haven't talked to you in
a while, but it's good to see you. Yes.
I was hoping somebody was from
Australia, and there you are. Brisbane,
Australia. It's another continent.
Wonderful. So good to have you guys. We
are. I mean, we're always worldwide,
guys, but we are really worldwiding
today. I just made that up. We're really
doing it today. Oklahoma, good to see
you. We love our uh our peeps in
America, too. So, good to have you here.
>> Love to do all these welcomes. And
unfortunately, we started here late and
we have to get to some things. I must
get to them. But it's good to see you
here. Long Beach, California. Good to
see you. And is E. Uh, yes. Praise. It
went up so fast. Ethiopia said,
I think that's a one. Praise God for
you. Oh, no. Somebody's saying, "Welcome
to the person coming from Ethiopia." All
right. Well, if this is your first time,
you're going to learn about us. Uh,
that's brother Terry saying it. Um, so
you're going to hear all about us today.
You'll get to learn at the beginning of
the divine worship service. So, stay
tuned because you'll get to learn every
a lot of things about us there. um and
so and see if you are interested um in
some different small groups and
ministries that we have going on or
different programming that we have going
on during the week. But stay tuned
because you will hear all about that at
the beginning of the divine worship
service.
>> And I and I will just say since you
brought it up, those of you that haven't
uh were not able to see the presentation
from last night,
>> uh we definitely encourage you to go
back and check it out. As you see people
are commenting in the chat.
>> So um go check it out. It's three parts.
It was amazing.
>> Um, and last night was the
>> the third part.
>> Yeah.
>> Part three,
>> the temporary finale.
>> Yes. Welcome from Greece. I'm sorry.
Some are coming up as you're talking.
>> Yes. And all right. And from another
part um Southeast Queensland, Australia,
we have quite a few Australians
>> um worshiping with us today. Welcome,
guys. I know it's it's early early
Sunday morning where you are. It's like
3:00 a.m. I think. I think I think I
think so. Um, but we love visiting
Australia and our time there. So,
welcome. Good to see you guys here.
Never been to Brisbane, though. Never
been to Brisbane. Okay, Ethiopia, it is
your first time. Welcome. You are going
to learn so much about Living Man
Church. It's so good to see you here
again with us. We actually have to do um
a second and first reading for a
membership. Uh tr one is a a first
reading coming in and um one is one
second reading
>> second reading going out
>> and Lisa yes the slides are now
available on Patreon. So um right under
the um the description of the video
you'll see the link to the slides.
>> All right.
Okay. So, we have unfortunately one
going out, but she's still our viewing
audience, but she's going to be working
with the local church in Brazil. And
this is Kayla Mahesia
and she's transferring from LMLC to um I
it's in the language and so um I don't
want to mess it up but to uh a church in
Brazil and yeah central de Santa Teresa
that I can say Brazil but the first one
I can't really say so in Brazil. So this
is the second reading for her
>> and the first reading uh to LMOC from
Jason Diggs from um the Kat Katosen
View 7th Day Adventist Church. Kosen
View.
>> Okay,
>> that's what it looks like. It says
Ktosen. So that's the first reading for
Jason. And for Kayla, this is the second
reading. So we need to um Well, you need
to make a motion. So, we'll make a
motion to accept Kayla's transfer out of
Living Mana. Um, we're going to have one
of our members um uh make the motion and
then someone else second and then we'll
go ahead and vote that through.
So, um I know you guys are a little bit
delayed. Um,
and by the way, while we're waiting for
that, um, I do want to
just ask everyone if they would, um,
just
pause for a second. Well, not even for a
second. Throughout the s the the service
today, I'd like for you to uh, lift up,
it's a very special unspoken request. Um
but um we have a a a situation with one
of our members and we just want to lift
uh that particular member in prayer. So
we can't say anything
um you know publicly but we would
definitely like for you to just be
praying for this special member um at
this time
>> in their situation
>> at this moment. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> So we do have a motion.
>> Yes, we do. Um, and uh, do we have a
second?
Okay, so we've got a motion. We're
looking for a second.
>> I second it.
>> Okay,
>> Second it. Yeah.
>> And, uh, we'll go ahead and, uh, take
the vote. So, all in favor of um,
Kayla's transfer
um to her church in Brazil. Just go
ahead and put that one in the chat.
And uh sis, if you're watching, of
course, you know, we're going to um we
will uh miss you, but we know that
you're not really going anywhere,
>> right?
>> Um so,
>> just off the books.
>> Yep.
>> But presently here.
>> Yes.
>> So, okay. Uh one in the chat and the
ones are coming in. So, I see them.
>> I see them. I see them. So,
uh it is
official.
Um
and uh Sister Kale, may God continue to
use you and bless you in the local
church there.
>> Um
>> absolutely.
>> And uh use you as a light to to continue
his work.
>> Amen.
>> Amen. Amen.
Um, we have
Sister Denise to bring on, but first
want to do the t-shirt message.
>> Okay. Pray, wait, trust. God has a plan.
>> Amen.
>> That is very simply said and I've of
course worn it before um but it just
we can never get enough of this message
because um as you know we are very
anxious people. You know, I think since
sin has entered, we're very anxious
people.
>> Uh, we worry. We try to take things in
our own hands. We don't wait. We don't
trust. It's just like just stop and be
still. I should make a t-shirt out of
what I want this verse I want to say.
Um, but and I don't know where it's
found, but where it says I think it's in
Psalms, but you can correct me or
somebody can correct me. Um, wait, wait,
I say on the Lord. Meaning,
>> it's almost like he's overemphasizing
wait like when you don't know the
direction God wants you to go in or if
he if you don't know what to do next,
seek him continually to seek him. be
very just be very let to have spiritual
ears to hear him and and he may speak
through situations or through certain
events or things happening you know you
know but the Holy Spirit I know my
experience I can't speak for everybody
but I don't you know I'm sure like
>> I feel the Holy Spirit impresses things
on my heart like be emotionally
sensitive like it the Holy Spirit is so
soft and gentle this is my experience
that
even and a lot of times it's going
against what I originally think I want
or what I need to do. The Holy Spirit
will come so softly and it's so
lovingly and kind and gentle, but you
feel so compelled
>> to go that way. I still have a decision.
I can still make a a different decision
what the Holy Spirit wants. But it's a
certain way the Holy Spirit just relates
to us as humans. And again, I'm speaking
for myself. I don't know what
everybody's
um I know God's not a boring God that he
does things the same way. So I don't
know if the Holy Spirit approaches
everyone the same way, but I know that's
the way he does for me.
>> So wait, trust God has a plan.
>> Amen.
>> Somebody needs to hear that today.
>> I always have to hear that every day
almost.
So, all right, we are going to bring on
we're going to start um may not be every
Sabbath, but we're going to be
highlighting different ministries within
um the LMLC church. So, you guys because
sometimes, you know, just so you will be
aware of what's going on and what the
ministry is doing. And so, Sister Denise
is going to come on and talk to us about
the um Living Mana newsletter
that she is a part of producing and
putting together. So, we would like to
invite Sister Denise on at this time.
>> Hi.
>> Hello.
>> You know,
>> how are you? I'm fine. Thank you. Hello,
pastor. Hello, first lady.
>> So, we can't hear you.
>> It's okay. It's okay. We do have them.
They're right there. We were so busy
making sure we were miked and the audio
was good that we forgot we had a guest.
All right, we we will hear you. We see
you smiling. The audience sees you
smiling and they can hear you, too. So,
>> now
>> they're gonna can say, let's see. All
right.
>> Now, right.
>> All right. We can hear you.
>> Yes, we can. Okay. So,
>> you can hear me now, right? Yes, we can
hear you now. So, tell us all about the
newsletter. Tell the audience all about
the newsletter.
>> So, Living Mana Online Church now has a
newsletter.
And it's considered a slice of Living
Mana. It is called Mana Connect. And
what we do at Mana Connect, we are a
unique ministry that actually allows
connection. Think of it as a newsroom
for excuse me all the ministries. It's a
opportunity for inreach and outreach.
>> Okay. All right. So, um it's so so the
and so how do um members or viewing
audience get to see this newsletter?
Like how can they
>> how do they get connected with LMLC
connect living connect? Yes.
Absolutely. So to get connected to manic
connect we have several ways. You can
either reach out there should be a link
coming up in the chat and you can reach
out and click the link in the space for
the newsletter.
>> Okay.
>> You can also if you are connected with
our text text the letter text the word
actually newsletter.
>> Okay. You can also email the newsletter
at newsletter
living mana church living mana.urch.
You can also in about a week or so be
able to go right into our church
platform, our church home mighty network
and there will be a space that will be
created just for you the viewing
audience
being able to interact with the
newsletter. Learn more about the
newsletter, ask questions about the
newsletter, tell us what you want to see
more in the newsletter. A great way to
connect with our contributors, uh, to
glean more information,
and really have the opportunity to
interact, to grow, and to learn
together, and to really have that
inreach and outreach that I believe is
so vitally important to the church.
That that sounds wonderful and I love
that it's going to be on Mighty Network
so that they can they can read it and
see it there um or I'm sorry view it and
see it there um as well because that is
our virtual church home. And so when
they're there they can see uh the
newsletter and then also see all the
other things that are going on on mighty
networks especially if they're new and
they can really learn about the church.
So that's an amazing way. Um or you like
you said they can get it emailed to them
or if they sign up for um to get text
alerts that if you text what was it
again? If you text what word?
>> Text newsletter. Newsletter.
>> News. Just newsletter guys. Don't forget
it. Just text newsletter. Um and then
you will be able to get the newsletter.
And this is coming out once a month.
>> Absolutely.
>> It comes out once a month. In fact, our
January letter has already been is
already out. And it's wonderful. I mean
it's so funny. pastor was speaking
yesterday about religious liberty and
Shaunin who's my partner in the
newsletter Shaine did an article on
religious liberty warning and it's just
amazing to see how the Holy Spirit
especially in this church more than I've
seen anywhere else really is on the same
wavelength when it comes to the
messaging
>> that we want to share with people uh the
love that we want to expose people to
the inclusivity that we have here at
Living Mana. And that's why for me, Mana
Connect is so such an easy extension of
who Living Mana is. So, I I want to put
a plug here. Uh if um you are interested
in submitting a story, contributing,
being part of the newsletter, you have
any questions, this is a wonderful
outreach evangelical ministry as well to
share with people who aren't necessarily
Adventists or Christian,
>> right? an opportunity to see who we are,
that we aren't cult, that we aren't
fuddy duddy, that we are just people
like you going through the same ups and
downs. Check out what the men's ministry
did as far as their article and where
they are as far as their walk. Look
through um what's in your trunk with
sister Joanne. Uh we have a photo of
theology app for uh that's a wonderful
app that pastor does that we use for our
game section. Um, please come be part of
this ministry because this ministry is a
part and extension of you.
>> Okay. And I heard you have a video and I
want to say Mental Health Monday wants
to uh write something too. We
>> But I guess Wonderful.
>> Yeah. Yeah. That'll be in one of the
editions. It doesn't have to. Yeah. Let
I love that the men's ministry is is
doing has done something. But you have a
video that uh you want to
>> I believe there's a video.
Yeah, that would be great to run right
now.
>> Yes.
>> Amen.
>> In a world filled with noise,
uncertainty, and constant motion, God
still invites us to pause and be fed.
Mana connect is more than a newsletter.
It's a place of nourishment, connection,
and spiritual renewal. Each month, Mana
Connect brings our church family
together, exploring faith, strengthening
values, and walking boldly in truth
during critical times. From men breaking
bread in brotherhood to voices of
encouragement lifting hearts, ministry
is alive, active, and growing through
messages like what's in your trunk.
We're reminded that freedom begins when
we release what God never asked us to
carry. With upcoming events, featured
media, and a thriving online community,
Mana Connect keeps you connected to what
matters most. Because this journey of
faith was never meant to be walked
alone. Mana connect, nourished by the
word, strengthened by community,
connected through Christ.
All right, that's Yeah, that's
wonderful. That's exciting. I know our
viewing audience and members are looking
forward uh to continue to get Mana
Connect. So remember guys, uh you can um
text uh newsletter if you've signed up
for text alerts or you hopefully in a
week or so you'll be able to uh get it
through um you will you can also get it
through email and then you will and then
you will will be getting it you can also
view it on mighty network. So we are
just happy about uh mana connect that's
exciting uh that we have a newsletter.
Uh, Sister Denise, if you're if you're
still there, do you have any closing
words for us?
>> No, I actually the only thing I would
say to the audience that's listening is
to please feel free to ask any
questions. Feel free to visit, feel free
to um provide insight in regards to the
newsletter. And please remember that the
newsletter is an extension of the Living
Mana online church ministry. We just
want to be the eyes and the ears and we
just want to bring this message of love
and prophecy to the world. Thank you so
much for giving us the opportunity to do
that.
>> All right. Yes. Thank you for doing
that. It's a blessing.
>> All right. Well, thank you again and I
think we are going to open for prayer so
that we can officially start um our
Sabbath school and answer some of your
questions. This is a question and
answer. Um I'm doing mental health
questions. Pastor is doing Bible
questions. Um I'll be also taking some
mental health or relationship questions
in the chat. I don't know how many Bible
questions you have, but you know, feel
free to like ask questions in the chat
like you know you're this is together.
This is Sabbath school. We're doing this
together. So, um, if he's answering
something, if I'm answering something
and you have a follow-up question,
please ask it in the chat. We want to,
uh, do this together.
>> All right. So, we're going to pray and
and start start our Sabbath school,
start answering questions.
>> Yeah. Let's pray. Heavenly Father, thank
you, Lord, for giving us this
opportunity, Lord, to to come together,
to study together, to pray together,
Lord. And, um, Lord, as we open this SA
school uh, with question and answers,
Lord, we pray that you would guide our
thoughts. And Lord, I just want to lift
up um
uh the situation with one of our
members, Lord, and just pray that
>> your spirit will will would intervene,
Lord, and just um
>> send the spirit of peace, of comfort,
Lord, and
um just again, Lord, intervene in that
situation.
Um and remove the plans of the enemy.
>> Yes.
>> Um confound them, Lord. and remind us,
Lord, that all things work together for
the good of those that love you. So,
Lord, we we lift this prayer
um and trust it will be answered because
we pray it in your name. Amen. And amen.
>> Amen. Amen.
>> All right. So, you're going first.
>> Do you want to go first?
>> Uh no.
>> All right. No.
>> Um so, uh once again, you guys, you
know, feel free to to put questions in
the chat. I'm going to start with um
this question on Revelation chapter 10.
So it says in Revelation 10, the angel
tells John to prophesy again. If the
Millerite movement fulfill the first
proclamation, what exactly is the full
scope of the again? And how do we know
when that second proclamation is fully
complete? So to give a little bit of uh
background um in Revelation chapter 10,
there is uh a vision of John receiving a
book from an angel. Um John is told to
eat the book and as he eats this book,
it's going to be sweet in his mouth but
bitter in his belly.
So he takes the book, he eats it, and
then he says, "As soon as I ate it, it
was sweet in my mouth but bitter in my
belly." So it tasted good, but the
experience afterward was a bitter one.
And this is what we typically describe
as uh the great disappointment
um of 1844.
Um and we don't just kind of pull that
out the hat, right? There's context to
this vision. There is timing to this
vision. In other words, this vision uh
takes place at a particular junction in
the book of revelation that lets us know
it is exactly around this time period
that this event is happening.
Um and so uh this great disappointment
was the understanding that in 1844 Jesus
was going to come again. This was not an
adventist teaching. This was a teaching
that was being proclaimed by people from
various denominations
um across America and around the world.
And so when October 22, 1844 came and
Jesus did not come, it was a great
disappointment,
>> right? You would think that with such a
an event like that happening, this would
be the end of whatever movement was, you
know, associated with that.
>> Instead,
that disappointment has become one of
the cornerstones
of our church, right? M
>> the idea that you must prophesy again
was almost as if the angel was saying
listen
>> you're going to have an experience.
>> Um in fact in that same chapter
there seven angels that utter something
and then they're told to seal it up.
Don't write it.
>> So here is something now that
has not been revealed. It is spoken but
not been revealed.
And the angel says, "Eat this book. It's
going to be sweet in your mouth, but
experience is going to be bitter in your
belly."
>> And that almost verbatim describes the
experience uh of 1844 where you have
this great this this what we suppose was
a failure of prophecy, but there was
something that the people of that time
did not understand.
>> There was something that the pioneers
did not understand. And it was only
afterward that they gained understanding
of where they went wrong in the
prophecy.
>> And as a result of this
um
this prophesy again
would happen almost immediately after
the great disappointment.
>> We've got understanding now. We
understand what happened and
now everything makes even more sense.
>> We got to go forth with this message
into the whole world. The end of this
second proclamation which is going on
right now is the second coming of Jesus
Christ.
>> Right? And that is the context of
Revelation chapter 14
>> which says, "I saw another angel um uh
coming down from heaven having the
everlasting gospel to preach unto them
that d on the earth to every nation,
kindred, tongue and people." This is
that second proclamation where this
message is to go into all the world with
the correct understanding of what
happened in 1844, which by the way is
what opened up the heavenly sanctuary.
Mhm.
>> Um I will say this that
uh the the
prophecy concluding in 1844
had its initial fulfillment like the
first part of that prophecy was the 70we
prophecy which pointed to the first
coming of Christ. And if you look at the
events of that first coming of of the uh
surrounding the first coming of Christ
and compare them to the events
surrounding 1844
um and they're both one prophecy. So the
2300 day prophecy the the first 490
years of that prophecy leads to Christ.
The remaining 1810 brings you to 1844.
If you take those two benchmarks and
look at the events that happened, they
parallel in an uncanny way. And what I
mean by that is that as you look at the
disciples,
they thought
that the 70we prophecy was going to be
fulfilled in Jesus setting up his
kingdom on earth. Mhm.
>> And even though Jesus told them, "I'm
going to die. I'm going to die. I'm"
They just didn't believe it, they were
like, "Uh, yeah, no, something else
going to happen." Their understanding of
prophecy was off. So when Jesus died, it
led to a great disappointment.
>> Right. And this great disappointment
should have been the death nail to the
movement. Jesus is dead now.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. That's it. Like go home. There's
nothing left. But instead it becomes the
very cornerstone of the early church.
Why? Because Jesus two days later he's
raised from the dead.
And it is two disciples
walking on the road to
>> Emmas
>> that have an encounter with Jesus
where they begin to understand where
they went wrong. Mhm.
>> Just as after the great disappointment,
there were um two men walking across the
cornfield ashamed, embarrassed because
they had gotten the prophecy wrong
>> because they believe they had gotten the
prophecy wrong. When as they were
walking across that cornfield,
the revelation that the sanctuary
was not the earth, but that there was a
temple in heaven. Mhm.
>> And this is what was occurring in 1844.
Jesus moving from holy to most holy
place ministry.
That realization was like, we got to go
prophesy again. We got to go tell the
world.
>> And as you can imagine, when the
disciples are talking about Jesus has
been raised from the dead and he's in a
heavenly temple now,
>> you can imagine the gains saying, "Sure,
this is a face saving effort because you
were wrong." And all of a sudden now,
yeah, Jesus is in a heavenly temple.
>> Come on, y'all are making stuff up
>> to save face.
>> Save face, right?
>> Um, which is exactly what they said
about the Meerite movement
>> uh post 1844, right? And they say to
this day, you guys are making stuff up
because it's just your way of saving
face. Mhm.
>> But what are the odds that the ending of
the 70 weeks and the ending of the 2300
days, which is part of one prophetic
time prophecy known as the 2300 day time
prophecy, literally parallel
>> in such an uncanny way.
>> That is beyond coincidence. Mhm.
>> So, uh long answer to that question, but
uh hopefully you understand now what the
prophesy again
um ma uh means. Let me just tack on to
this. How could a non-adventist be
convinced of prophesy again being
applied to 1844?
>> So, I would not Oh, and the fact that
they don't believe anything about the
meite movement. Yeah, I wouldn't I would
never share something like that with
someone who is not first convicted about
1844. So, I would never start there. I
would start back in Daniel chapter 2,
>> right? Because
let me let me add here, okay, that when
whenever you're discussing 1844, I was
watching a um uh one of these
anti-adventist um videos uh that came
out just this week, actually,
>> just recently. And uh the the guy was
speaking about Daniel 8:14
>> and how it has nothing to do with um
with uh you know what Adventists say it
has to do with um and that the little
horn is is Greece and it's not Rome and
Rome has nothing to do with Daniel
chapter chapter 8. M
>> um and I was like, man, that that is
that that's a wow. That I was just like,
wow. Like,
>> how do you walk away from the Bible with
those kind of conclusions,
>> right? But you know what's interesting
is that he started in Daniel 8:14
without really unders I'm not going to
say without understanding but
in order to rightly understand Daniel 8
you have to first rightly understand
Daniel 2
>> and Daniel 7
>> and Daniel 9 and Daniel 11 because the
entire book of Daniel is is a it is a
doing it. It's not just separate
prophecies here and there.
>> The book of Daniel has one prophecy.
>> That is it. It's one prophecy
>> that goes into more detail as it moves.
>> That's right. every chap Daniel 2 7 8 9
and 11 are all giving you different
views
>> and and different um different
>> greater detail
>> greater detail of the very same
prophecy.
>> Right.
>> So if you get Daniel 2 wrong, you get
everything else wrong.
>> Right. Right.
>> So where would I start? I wouldn't start
by saying, "Oh, did you know that the
prophesy again um was referring to the
Meerite movement?" That just seems like,
"How could that be? You're making that
up." No, let's go back to uh Daniel 2,
build on Daniel, build on Daniel 2, then
Daniel 7, then Daniel 8. And once you
can get a person to understand why
Daniel 8 is connected to Daniel 7,
connected to Daniel 2,
>> then you've set the foundation for them
to understand the deeper things of the
book of Revelation.
>> So because I only listened to little a
little snippet of that that you were
listening to. So I'm just hearing this
for the first time, too. So for them,
they want to put grease in there. So
that takes
>> correct
>> it off of the little horn.
>> Yep. So
>> why do they want to do that? Yeah. In
order for
>> I mean so where do they put So they so
they put instead of the little horn they
put it on Greece,
>> right? So
>> and where does that take them?
>> Yeah. The time of the end
>> I'm saying after that after they put it
there then what? Like that doesn't make
sense. So
>> the time of the end is Greece. And so
what they do and this is this is called
predtoism. This is what this is.
>> Okay.
>> What they do is they say in Daniel 2
it's Babylon and then me and then the
Median Empire. the me the Mes
>> and then Persia and then Greece.
>> So they separate the Mes and the
Persians
>> to make them two different kingdoms so
that they can end with
>> and if you end with Greece in Daniel 2,
then you can end with Greece in Daniel 7
and you can end with Greece in Daniel 8,
>> right? But if Daniel 2 doesn't end with
Greece, if the Meo Persian Empire is one
empire according to the Bible,
>> then where they say when ne when Babylon
falls, your kingdom is given divided and
given to the Mes and the Persians,
>> not to the Mes but the Mes and the
Persians. Then Daniel 2 must end with
with Rome, which means Daniel 7 must end
with Rome, which means your
interpretation of Daniel 8 only ending
with Greece really
>> is not consistent
>> and get you in a lot of trouble.
>> Right? So,
um, in essence, y'all,
Daniel 8 or or that
>> Revelation chapter 10 prophecy is like
it's kind of like the trigonometry where
you want to start with, you know, the
basic math of Daniel chapter 2,
>> right?
>> Don't introduce someone to trigonometry
before they learn the basics of the of
of math, right? Okay.
>> So, Daniel 2 78 and then that's how I
would approach uh that prophesy again
>> to a non-adventist
>> to an adventist. Yeah.
>> All right. It's been a lot of time here,
but okay.
Let's look at some of the questions that
you guys have sent in for mental health
or relationships. So, there's a question
here. It says, "Many teens today feel
torn between honoring their parents and
trying to figure out who they are. How
can a Christian teen set healthy
boundaries, express their emotions, and
develop their own identity without
feeling like um they are being
rebellious and disrespectful? Very good
question. Very good question. So, um
first of all, I it was interesting how
this question worded it. said, um, "How
can how can Christian teens set healthy
boundaries?" And really,
it's how and really when I when I hear
that, I'm thinking, how should uh
Christian parents
adapt to their children when they become
teens
and set healthy boundaries? Meaning, and
I said this last night at the end of it,
you know, our children are not born
Christians. They're not born Seventh Day
Adventists. Now, we teach them from a
young age like this is God. This is
let's pray. Let's, you know, this is
Bible stories. We take them to church.
This is Sabbath school lessons,
whatever. You know, we're teaching them
all these things. But you have to give
them space
to make their own decision to choose God
for themselves. And sometimes they have
to figure things out. And as Christian
parents,
um, we don't give them that space. And
that
that causes them never to really choose
for themselves to have that intimate
individual relationship with Jesus
that's outside of their parents. Um, and
so for the Christian teen, I mean, in
some cultures, it's very difficult to
stand up for yourself as a Christian
teen. Even if you're trying to be
respectful, they think the mere fact
that you're even respectfully asking for
anything is disrespectful. And so you
guys, maybe some of you that are in that
are part of those cultures know what I'm
talking about. Um, and so, but it's
still that's the way you're supposed to
do it is to um come to a parent and and
let them know that they you believe in
God. You you want a relationship with
God or you're you're seeking that out,
but you're also trying to figure things
out. So just parents allowing their
child to have open honest communication
and not condemn them or not like freak
out if they say like I'm trying to
figure this Christianity thing out. I'm
trying to even figure out my belief in
God out. Give them space to do that
because and it's God's responsibility to
prove himself to us as individuals. You
know what I'm saying? That's why the
Holy Spirit comes and is our comforter
and our friend and you know it's like
God is wooing not just us but our
children to him. So kind parents after
you kind of help lay a foundation for
them, step out of the way a little bit.
Of course, they're in your home and
there's there are rules and you know,
you're not going to just allow
everything to go just abs. They're
teenagers, but you still can step away.
They're not little kids anymore. So as
your children grow up, you have to you
as they get older, you have to pivot and
adjust. I think that the burden is more
on the parents. Even though this is
supposed to be a teenager asking, the
burden is more on the parents
for they have to adjust to where their
their child is now. They're not little
kids anymore. They're teenagers. Respect
that stage of their life. And then as
they become young adults, you're going
to have to pivot and respect that stage
of their life. And when they become
adults, married, have their own
children, you have to respect that stage
of life as well. So it's I feel like the
burden is more on the parents
>> like we have to do that learning curve
like as soon as they come into this
world our whole focus is just like keep
them alive and teach them about Jesus
you know as Christian parents
>> um and so we and then there's a point
where we have to like okay they're
becoming older we have to love them the
best thing parents Christian parents can
do is to have an authentic relationship
with Jesus themselves and have the
character of Jesus and the way we're
treating our children that that is
enough in itself to
introduce the proper uh Jesus to them
and for them to want to know that Jesus
because you have modeled the character
of Jesus and you live the character of
Jesus every day before them. So
>> that's the answer to that question. All
right, I want to go ahead and jump to
this question uh in the chat and uh it
says, "I have a question, pastor, about
the conclusion from last night with the
10 horns. Uh what were you trying to
conclude with the spiritual application
of how it connects with the final events
uh for today or now?" Um, so for those
of you that didn't watch last night's um
message,
>> I don't know how well I'm going to be
able to like, you know, juice this down.
>> Well, it'll make the other ones curious,
be like, "Huh, let me go see that. Let
me go check it out."
So um in essence uh the the the
point that I was making the the the
argument I was laying out was that in
the Old Testament, right? We talked
about these three stages of this
abomination of desolation like event.
First in the Old Testament connected
with the 70 years and the 70 weeks, then
with the dark ages and finally at the
end of time. And what we saw across all
three was that just as and we used the
parable, you know, we basically were t
using the parable of the when an unclean
spirit leaves
um is put out of a is
put out of a man that when he comes
back, he's looking for his house and
wants to go back into his house. He
finds it empty, swept, and garnished or
swept and garnished, but it's empty. and
he brings seven other demons within with
him and it makes the first state of the
man worse or the last state of the man
worse than the first. So we took that
analogy and we were like this happened
with Israel when they allowed idolatry
into the house of God into the temple
specifically and God allowed Babylon to
in essence enter into that temple as a
result of their sin and destroy the
temple
and they serve 70 years in captivity.
When they come out of captivity, this is
synonymous with the demon being cast
out, if you will. Babylon is fallen.
They get to go back to the house. They
they they
fix the house up, right? They rebuild
the temple. They furnish it. Uh it is
swept. It is garnished. But
they're now waiting for the presence of
Jesus.
>> And in waiting for the presence of
Jesus,
uh when Jesus finally comes, they reject
him. And so Jesus says, "Your house is
left unto you desolate. your house is
left unto you desolate. Here's what we
see here. Number one, that between that
time of the of the of the children of
Israel coming back into the house, they
had learned their lesson about idolatry,
about paganism, and they in essence
build up this intense hatred for
paganism.
But they felt that all they had to do
was hate paganism. And that is what
constituted righteousness. So when Jesus
comes, they reject him. He's not in the
house. Their whole religion is based on
how much you hate how much you hate
paganism and how much you hate the
Gentiles and how much you hate the
idoltors.
This
is a form of godliness without the
power. Right? And and basically what I
was showing was this is how the devil
operates
both in the last prophecy for Israel and
then we see it during the dark ages
>> where the early church did the literally
did the same thing. I'm talking about
the early church of the you know in the
days of Christ. I'm talking about 300,
400, 500 AD on into the dark ages
>> where they began this culture war of
overthrowing pagan idols, you know,
trying to get pagans out of their
country,
>> out of their nations
because now to them nation is the new
house.
>> So we got to get the demon out and the
demon was paganism. So whereas paganism
allowed religious liberty for everybody
around them, when Christians got a hold
of that,
>> right,
>> religious liberty for nobody but the
Christian,
>> and what happened in in the church of
the dark ages is they believed that
their hatred for paganism
amounted to righteousness with God.
>> They didn't have to be nice. They didn't
have to be holy. They I mean, they
didn't have to, you know, care for
people. All that was all that was
important was we're getting rid of
paganism out of the nation. Out of we're
getting rid of the pagans. That is what
righteousness is. And of course we see
Jesus calling that very system the
abomination of desolation. So then how
does this tie into what's going on today
in our society with apostate
Protestantism? They are doing literally
the same thing. Mhm.
>> They believe that their position their
positions against the pagan, right,
>> against the atheist,
>> qualifies or qualifies, I should say,
for righteousness,
>> so hey, as long as I hate the, you know,
the the people that I think have want
nothing to do with God, as long as I
hate the atheists, as long as I I'm on
the right side, side of the culture war,
then I'm righteous with God.
>> And this is what Christianity has boiled
down to today is, you know, if you got
the right positions, then you're holy
and you're on God's side.
>> That is not righteousness, right? That
is false righteousness. That is the
abomination of desolation in its final
iteration.
And that final iteration is not full.
There is more coming. The seven other
demons or I should say the three unclean
spirits like frogs
>> will be the final event that fills the
entire house with so many demons
that it cannot be counted.
>> Right? So, in essence, that was the the
basis of last night's message was we saw
it in the rejection of Christ. We saw it
in the dark ages. And what we're seeing
now in American Christianity is
literally a repeat of the abomination of
desolation during the dark ages and of
what the Jews did in the, you know, in
the in the years leading up to Christ.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. So hopefully that puts a bowl on
what I was teaching last night. Um just
so it can be clear in your mind, right?
>> This is what we were showing uh in that
study
>> in that part three.
>> Okay, I have one in the chat. I have
more here, but that have come in, but I
have one that was just live in the chat.
And because this is interactive and
Sabbath school, I want to to meet you
guys where you're at because who knows
if the people that ask these other the
questions are here. You're here. So,
okay. All right. Uh, my two brothers and
I have been uh praying about six years
for a rift in our about a rift in our
relationship. Recently, one brother
stopped praying because it seems very
clear my brother I'm assuming you're
talking about the other brother is a
narcissist. Advice. Well,
um, first of all, I don't have a lot of
information here to confirm that, and I
wouldn't do that over the air anyways
to, but to even have an idea if the
brother is a true narcissist, I have to
say that's a term that is thrown around
so much. There are criteria that needs
to be met to really be diagnosed with to
be a narcissist. But in this in our this
day and age and in our culture, like
growing up, had had you ever heard the
term narcissists? We had no idea what
that was. However, but there are true
narcissists. There really are. We Okay,
I was going to say something, but I'm
going leave it there. But we have
experience that here in America on a
regular basis. We see things like that.
So, but there are there is criteria to
be a narcissist. And your brother may
not he may or he may not be a
narcissist, but you're seeing
characteristics of narcissism or some of
the traits that um make up a narcissist.
And truly, you're doing all that you can
do. You're praying. You're still
praying. the other brother. Um, you
could encourage him to continue to pray
because there's nothing that you or your
other brother can do to change the other
brother that you believe is a narcissist
or at least has those characteristics um
of a narcissist. So, I'm sure the other
brother in your and you and your other
brother's eyes is very difficult to deal
with, is not very humble, maybe is so
prideful, can't see what other people
are trying to say about things, and the
list can go on and on and go on and on.
Um, honestly, that's all you can do.
Even if a narcissist is prey, even if a
narcissist comes into therapy, there's
work that a therapist can do with the
narcissist. it is a uh real uphill steep
battle if you will because um it's it's
the way their their brain is wired and a
lot of and and then when you study
narciss narcissist um behavior it does
come from um a lot of times it comes
from a trauma that um that person has
experienced earlier in life, early
childhood trauma, early childhood
trauma. um and these thoughts and the
way that they the way that they think
and the way their brain is wired started
at a much earlier age and so that's a
longer process to be able to work that
through everything it everything is
possible by the grace of God so anyone
can change nobody is stuck in one
behavior I would say working with a
narcissist is a much more challenging
work so for you and your brother you
pray to the most powerful God to help
your relationship with your other um as
much as possible. And then as it gets
closer, hopefully um if you ever have an
open door, you can encourage him uh to
to also seek help and maybe as you're
praying the holy he'll respond to the
Holy Spirit and just want to uh work on
his relationships with people and that
will lead him to want to get help on his
own. So that is the answer I can give
for that. Totally switching gears here
into a relationship question.
Since you took two, I think I'm taking
two. All right. So,
it is okay. This person is asking, "Is
it fair to expect someone to make extra
efforts to rebuild trust after it's been
broken, a sort of probation, or once you
make the decision to forgive, should the
person have a clean slate?" So once you
have decided to forgive, yes the person
has a clean slate but a clean slate to
every day show you that they are that
they appreciate your forgiveness, your
grace that you've extended to them and
every day they have a clean a clean
slate to show you that they have really
changed and that they are sorry for what
they have done and they are distancing
themselves from that behavior. behavior
to ever hurt you again. Does that make
sense?
>> All right. So, that's that's a lot to
say about that.
>> Yeah.
>> So, it's fair to expect
you should see change. You should be
seeing change.
>> Um Yeah. All right. Go ahead.
>> Okay. Uh so,
in Daniel 12:4, knowledge increases at
the time of the end. How do we
distinguish between human technology and
advancement and the spiritual knowledge
God intended and what biblical criteria
determine what increase fulfill which
increase fulfills prophecy?
>> So, um you know this is something that a
lot of people have, you know, talked
about. Hey, here's a sign of the end
times. Uh
knowledge is increasing
um and look at what's happening with
technology. Mhm.
>> But um I don't believe the Bible is
talking about technology
um in Daniel 12:4. What I believe the
Bible is talking about is the knowledge
of the gospel increasing.
Um
Jesus says right this gospel shall be
preached in all the world uh for witness
and then shall the end come. So
according to Jesus Jesus's own words,
the sign that the end will come is the
knowledge of the gospel going into all
the world. That fits Revelation chapter
14 uh verse 6 and 7 um which again
points to the everlasting gospel going
to every nation, kindred, tongue and
people and an understanding of what the
actual gospel is. Right? So it's not
that
an increase in technology is leading God
to say, you know what, it's time for me
to, you know, to come and end this all.
Um, no, it's not it's not about
technology
that goes into the that increases as a
sign of the end times. It is about the
knowledge of the gospel. And
remember
um that during the dark ages the
knowledge of the gospel had been
perverted,
right? And so it would make sense that
if if there was darkness in the dark
ages, then after the dark ages,
light
would be going into there would be an
increase in light, right?
and an increase in understanding. And
that's what we see happening. We see it
happening today. Um I think as we are
studying our own message, we're seeing
deeper levels of truth that verify,
right, the word of God. Um yeah,
Charles, knowledge of prophecy.
Knowledge of prophecy. Knowledge of
prophecy. Knowledge of the plan of
salvation. Um this is the knowledge that
the enemy I believe is trying to keep
away from the world
>> to keep the world in darkness.
>> Right?
>> Um so again that is the uh that is the
the
knowledge I believe is being increased.
Next I'm going to talk about uh this is
a a question about marriage
and the question is
um
actually
let me pull up um I can't find that
other question.
Yeah, I was going to do two questions in
one. But uh okay, let me talk let me
speak to this question and it's about uh
what does the Bible say about being
unequally yolked and you know is it all
right for you to marry someone outside
of your faith? Um so that's a question
that is that I think is is you know a
lot of people have that question on
their mind.
>> Um so several things here.
uh you know
some people will say well the Bible says
do not be unequally yolked with
unbelievers. So the question now becomes
what is an unbeliever? Okay.
>> Um and you might say well if we both
believe in God that should be good
enough
>> well then for some people that may mean
that you know uh a Muslim can marry a
Christian
>> because they both believe in their minds
in the same God. And some people say,
"No, we don't believe in the same God.
So, you know, that would not be
appropriate because we have different
faiths."
>> Um,
well, then what about uh a Jew a person
of Jewish faith and a Christian?
>> You know, would that be acceptable? And
again if you know for the Jewish person
who says I don't believe you know in
Jesus as the Messiah and the Christian
saying I do believe in Jesus as the
Messiah. You know
the
the thing that you that you need to
understand when you're yoking yourself
up with someone. Yeah. Can two walk
together except they be agreed? Mhm.
>> The thing that we need to understand is
that remember this is that when you get
married, you're talking about bringing
kids into the picture. And you know, if
your message
as parents to your children is, hey, you
know,
religion, you can be what you want to
be. You can be what you want to be. Like
in our minds, it's not that important.
>> They're going to walk away with, well,
yeah. Yeah. You know what? my mom was
this, my dad was this, and it didn't
really matter. So, it doesn't really
matter. Now, if that is your position,
then it would be consistent for you,
right, to be willing to marry someone
outside your faith if it's like, oh,
it's not a big deal. Mhm.
>> But if your position is that what we
have is biblical truth that should not
be compromised in any way,
>> then now you got to ask yourself, am I
willing to send the message to my
children? It's one thing if you're
already married, different story
altogether. But if you're not married,
you got to ask yourself, am I willing to
to put my children
uh in a position of showing them, hey,
it doesn't really matter if for me it
does really matter,
>> right? Um
so you might say, okay, well, yeah, they
have to be Christian.
>> All right, so now let's break it down to
the Christian category. Okay, so you're
both Christian, but one is Catholic and
one is one is Protestant.
one believes that you, you know,
traditions matter. The other one
believes that it's the Bible only.
>> Again,
um
how do you bring children into a
situation where if you have that kind of
conviction, you're like, and you you
want to pass that conviction on to your
children and of course you're not God.
You can't force your children to do
anything, right?
>> So, keep that in mind as well. We're not
saying you forced your kids, but what I
am saying is that the message you send
um to your children is really very
important. Not the message you send to
the world,
>> right? To those who are looking at your
example. Um,
Samson
was probably really in love with the
woman who was totally, you know, like,
>> hey, I really, really, really want to be
with this woman even though she is not
one of us.
>> Um, and I'm not saying that that always,
you know,
>> sometimes miraculous things happen.
Uh there are people who get married who
are on different pages when they get
married and by the grace of God they get
on the same page,
>> right? So it's not a cookie cutter thing
of this is what's going to happen if
this happens. But understand and I want
to bring it down to to
the most basic level.
Let's say you're both Adventists.
Let's just say you're both Adventists,
>> but one of you is like, "Yeah, you know,
church, whatever."
>> And the other one is like, "We're really
about, you know, I'm really about
church."
>> I would say y'all are probably not the
best fit,
>> right?
>> Because
>> Yeah. to be unequally yolked
like that.
>> You could be unequally yolked in so many
different ways
>> and still say that you're you're you
belief system is still a part of the
same religion, but
>> your individual walk is not
>> the same.
>> Yeah,
>> I want to say good information. I just
want to say um
>> on top of all of what you already said,
>> uh
>> hold on, hold that thought.
>> Okay. It's it's one thing if you know
you you're talking to someone who
they're like I'm really interested in
this and you know I'm talking about hey
I'm Baptist and I'm going to be Baptist
or I'm Methodist I'm going to be
Methodist and nothing you say is going
to change that it is what it is right
that's what I'm talking about that
situation because I understand
>> there's different scenarios and
different and nothing is a cookie cutter
case
>> but I'm talking about I'm I I guess I'm
speaking in the extreme of and it's not
an extreme but I'm saying all right here
is a person who says I am comfortable in
my faith and I will probably never
become your faith right that's what I'm
addressing
>> and then you got to ask yourself
am I willing to take this risk
of setting this kind of example for my
family that my love for
person a was greater than my
desire or my love for God,
>> my love for truth,
>> right? Those are the questions you got
to ask.
>> And again, even if you're in the same
system and you're on two different
paths,
>> right?
>> Those are the ones that end most in
disaster.
>> Yeah.
>> You're the same faith. You're just like,
"Okay, we're equally yolked." Not
realizing you weren't equally yolked.
>> You weren't really. I just wanted to say
on top of all of that good stuff that
you already said that, you know,
>> because
most of the divorces
>> I'm gonna have to go fast.
>> Most of the divorce is happening in
Adventist churches is not because an
Adventist is married to a Baptist or
>> it's Adventist divorcing Adventists. So
I just wanted to like really illustrate
that point. Right.
>> Right.
>> So I'm not saying, okay, that's an
excuse. What I'm saying is
>> you can be unequally yolked even within
the same religion. And if that's the
case, how much more if you're not the
same religion, right?
>> Well, people are getting divorced for a
lot of different reasons,
>> right? Not for religious reasons,
unequal yolk.
>> Hey, my lifestyle is this, your
lifestyle is this. We're in the same
church. We're in the same church, but
you're more this way. I'm more this way.
And that causes
>> problems. Right.
>> Right.
>> I was just going to say, you're not
allowed to touch me. I'm just kidding.
Um, I was going to say that,
you know, marriage, um, marriage is very
marriage is beautiful and it's wonderful
when you're married to the right person
and it's still hard.
>> I just think the way that's the way God
designed it. There's some things that he
wants to teach us. Um, and even though
you're both committed to to God and
you're and you're striving for the same
thing, it's beautiful and wonderful, but
you're still going to grow and learn and
sometimes learn some hard lessons
>> um that can can only kind of happen when
you become one with a person and you
have to uh have that self-sacrificing
love and and learn how to um just
learn how to
um not be selfish and work with another
person um that you love but you don't
see eye to eye with all the time. I'm
not talking about being equally yolked
and all that. So, I'm saying
>> that's on a normal marriage. It's it's
great. It's loving. It's it can be
wonderful and then it's still hard, but
it's a beautiful thing. It's a be you
have so much beauty in it that even
those hard things you you go through you
live through because it's such a
wonderful thing. And then if you go
through those hard things and you're not
equally yolked, like you can't come
together and pray together. I can't
imagine if I was a Christian and you
were not a Christian
or um you wanted to go pray I guess I
mean you wanted to go pray to Mary
instead of us praying to the God of
heaven together about something. how
difficult that would be because when we
are going through difficult times I'm
just using that as an example guys I'm
just using that as an example when we
are going through difficult times or
want to pray need to pray together it is
comforting when we both have the same
belief system and go before God together
it gives peace um in the marriage that
you've brought your issues together with
your spouse and laid it at the altar and
you can you can walk away with
confidence that God is going to do
something
>> absolutely you still have blind faith,
but you can walk away confidently with
blind faith that it's going to be done.
So, just wanted to add that little
>> uh spiritual caveat on all of that. So,
>> um and I will just say this as well. Um
so, Les Leslie, I don't know if I said
your name right, but uh wow.
And I'll just leave it at that. I will
just say wow. And I'mma go check that
out. So her question was
>> I was like do we know what you're
talking about?
I totally missed it.
>> Yeah. She said pastor the fact that the
Lisbon that Lisbon is in is the city of
Portugal which was responsible for the
terrible persecutions of Christians
>> in your opinion would that would you
attach that earthquake to God's
punishment.
>> So I've just never even thought about
that before.
>> The great Lisbon earthquake, right?
Okay. Um I'm going to go I need to look
at some time uh time factors but uh that
is a very
interesting
observation.
>> Yeah.
>> All right. Have another relationship
question and it's going on um trust. I
think this is a faith and trust deal.
Okay. uh day. Let's say it says, "How do
you rebuild emotional safety in a
marriage when forgiveness has happened
but trust hasn't returned at the same at
at the same pace?
Um what does healing look like when both
partners are trying uh but the hurt
still shows up in everyday
interactions?"
Okay. So I guess what this person is
saying is they've forgiven uh their
spouse, their partner in the
relationship, but they're still not uh
trusting. So again, not having a lot of
details, not knowing the timeline, if
this is a a recent like, okay, I'm
forgiving him or her uh but I still
don't trust. So rebuilding trust is a
process. kind of goes back to that other
question about uh forgiveness that I
answered earlier. So when you are uh the
person that has inflicted the uh pain
and caused the partner not to trust when
that partner again decides to forgive
you um like I answered in the other
question, you have a clean slate, but
now you have a clean slate to show this
partner again that you are terribly
sorry. um that you every day uh by God's
grace are starting that day off to show
them that you are trustworthy because
you're a changed person. Um and so even
though partner that was hurt, even
though you've forgiven that partner, for
you to trust,
it's going to take a process. And so if
it's a new situation that has happened,
um you're not just say, "Okay, I forgive
you." And then you automatically just
trust. Again, you it's a daybyday
um situation where the more you see them
uh being transparent and uh just not
hiding anything or just ba in a balance
going over not over the top in a bad
way, but going over the top and showing
you that um you're not keeping any
secrets or you're an open book. you're
always knowing their location. And you
know, I tell my uh married couples when
they're in therapy with me and there's
no there's both always know the the
passcode to um the the password or
passcode to the phone to the email.
Well, not that you're going in there
stocking looking for something, but if
you have to happen to go into their
phone for something or go into their
email for something or whatever, there's
total transparency on both sides. In
marriage, you don't keep secrets. You
both get to know
there's just no secrets. Like, there's
just no secrets. And so, um, as long
when you're learning how to trust again,
total transparency is key to beginning
to build that trust again. And um, and
that the partner that's having to to be
trusted again, they're okay with that.
They're like, "Hey, I'm an open book.
I'm a changed man. I'm a changed woman.
I my goal in moving forward and being
with you is not to ever hurt you again.
So I have no problem you reading myself,
you reading my texts, you reading my
emails, you you know coming to events
with me, whatever. I am an open book. I
am here for you. Once you're seeing that
type of behavior for some time, the
trust is being built day after day after
day. So trust can be torn down in a
moment and it takes time to build it
back up again.
>> Amen.
Um, and I do just want to point out, I
don't know if uh
uh Sogfic,
I don't know how to how to say that, but
um I I see you in the chat. I see that I
don't know if this is your first time
watching with us. Can you can you let me
know is this your first time?
Um
if not, I just want to welcome you.
>> Amen.
>> Uh he's uh he's actually I think you're
Catholic. Is that right? I look up here.
You said you were once Protestant, but
now you're a Catholic. So, um,
uh, if that is
if that is the case, either way,
>> I just welcome you to to to to
>> to to joining. I welcome I welcome you
um, joining us today. If it is your
first time watching,
>> LMLC church welcomes you. We're thrilled
that you are here.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Uh, and if you need to reach
out to me for any reason,
you may. Smile. Smile. All right. Um, so
was was that your
>> Yeah, that was the answer to that
question.
>> Okay. Um, so let me
um
I'm going to do one more question.
>> Okay.
>> Uh, and do you have another question
you're going to do or
>> um I might be able to do a quick one.
We'll see how long you do how long you
are. So if the great controversy began
with questions about God's character,
why does scripture say that sin will not
rise a second time when free will will
still exist in the new earth? What
guarantees eternal loyalty loyalty
without removing freedom?
>> Um
so uh okay, I see you. I don't even know
what I'm just saying. S O Gf
so fig. I don't know if but I see you. I
see you. Okay. Mhm.
>> Um
so here is what happens right
the the reason sin will not rise again a
second time
>> is not because God suddenly takes away
uh freedom of choice. Right? Um
it is as a result of our experience
with sin
that
we will never want to touch it
experience it again.
>> Right?
when when you experience the loss of a
loved one,
that uh that pain I think in and of
itself
would be enough for
most people
to in heaven say, "I never want anything
to do with sin again."
But the real thing that is going to keep
everyone from sinning again is what
Jesus endured on the cross on our
behalf.
>> Right? Our love for Christ,
what he went through on our behalf,
um
suffering what he did not deserve
to give us
that chance to live forever and ever.
Um remember this, angels are in heaven
right now and angels have freedom of
choice. Angels are not automations.
Angels are not robots,
>> right? They freely do the will of God.
And so the idea that wait a minute, you
know, like how is how is that going to
work? It's working right now, right?
There's no angel after Lucifer's
rebellion that was like, man, I should
have went with Lucifer.
>> Get get me out of this place. Right? Um,
in the same way in the new heaven and
earth, uh, there will be there will be
no rebellion because of the marks in
Jesus's hands will be the reminder of
the cost of sin. Right?
>> The fact that Jesus retains his humanity
forever in heaven, that means he's
forever a different creature, if you
will. He's still absolutely divine, but
he will have humanity with as a part of
him where that was not the case before
he came to this earth.
That sacrifice in and of itself, which
really angels did not know. Mhm.
>> Um the Bible says that angels desire to
look into the things of salvation that
that we are now experiencing because
they have never experienced loss.
>> That is the holy angels righteous.
They've never experienced loss.
When we get to heaven by the grace of
God,
>> sin will not be a desire. There will be
nothing pulling at us to say, you know
what, you really should.
>> It'll it'll all be gone,
>> right? And and there will be no
curiosity as to I wonder what will
happen if I disobey God. That question
is not going to be
>> we will all we know what happens
>> through experience. We will know.
>> We we through experience we know. So,
>> that's interesting when I just thought
about you answering that question just
made me think like when God says he'll
wipe all our tears from our eyes um
after after everything um is done, but
we'll never forget.
We're never going to forget.
>> And that's a good thing.
>> Yep.
>> That's a good thing.
>> No sin in heaven.
Um, I could answer another question, but
because our time has gotten away from
us, I can definitely carry it into uh
the next question and answer uh period.
But we are just thankful for all of your
questions. Um, by God's grace, hopefully
we answered them um to where it was
helpful and bene beneficial to you. Um,
we are getting ready to go into the
divine worship service. Don't want you
guys to go anywhere. We know we have
some first- timers here uh today and so
please continue to worship with us. Can
you tell us what your message is about
today? So, uh, the message today is
entitled the trans Christian movement.
And I know you're like, trans Christian?
What in
>> for our first timers who don't know
about you?
>> For the first timers who don't know
about me, about my style of preaching,
you will know that uh, it's not what you
think. Mhm.
>> And um I I believe you will be by the
grace of God as you listen to this
message, you will see that it is a
message that is desperately
that is needs to be heard by a lot of
people who
claim
to be
Christians.
>> Okay.
Okay. All right.
>> So yes. So, please continue to worship
with us. Like, subscribe and share.
Those three things like the uh channel
you are watching. Um
>> Living Mana on Living Mana YouTube
channel. Yes.
>> If you're watching on on Power of Glamb
YouTube channel,
>> like and subscribe, but
>> we're we're talking more service.
>> Yes. And Yeah. So, like, subscribe, and
share uh with your family and friends.
invite them to church and to come into
worship with you as we are about to go
into the divine worship service. So,
don't go anywhere.
>> Okay, let me say one last thing. I know
>> uh cuz I see that there's a there's a
question here that speaks to what we
were talking about earlier. My wife is
Baptist SDA. My concern is if she
doesn't believe what I believe, how
would that affect our relationship
spiritually? So, remember that Paul when
he's counseling, this is not for
believer and unbeliever, right? someone
who is married to someone who is who
doesn't believe the same as as that
person. He says that's not a cause for
divorce.
>> Okay?
>> It's not.
>> So please understand that. And then
please understand that through the grace
of God, right? Um
you can get to that place where you are
you are on the same page. But it can't
be by force.
>> No.
>> It can't be by argument. No.
>> It's got to be by prayer.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. pray,
study,
communicate,
>> love each other.
>> Love each other.
>> Um, but don't walk away thinking, "Oh,
well, if I'm married to someone who is
who doesn't believe as I do, that that
is grounds for divorce because it is
not.
>> It's not."
>> Yeah.
>> I have a story behind that, but I won't
share it right now. I don't think. Okay.
I guess I am. my my greatg grandmother,
loving, beautiful woman. Um
was married a second time. Um and when
she got married, she was an Adventist.
She was not uh but she became Adventist.
And at that time, one of the I think it
was a local elder, I don't think it was,
I don't know, it could have been the
pastor or elder, but they told her that
she's Adventist now, so she has to get a
divorce.
That was bad counsel.
>> And my
beautiful, loving, so spiritual, godly
great-g grandandmother did what she
thought was right because the godly
counsel from men of God uh told her to
do that. Um she had a great marriage,
wonderful man. She loved him and it was
it really um emotionally hurt her a lot
to do that. So, I'm just saying that um
that was something that I'm thinking now
this was like in the 50s.
>> Yeah. In the 50s. Um and so that was
just some very very bad counsel. So
that's just letting you know that you
are married. Um and um this is something
that God wants you to just show your
spouse uh his character and his love.
And so and God will do the rest. and you
just keep loving and being that good
person in your marriage. Um to be that
example
um and you said he's a Christian as
well. So um by God's grace he's loving
you. I said he did. It was a husband. I
just don't know why I assumed a husband.
By God's grace by God's grace he's that
that partner is loving you as well. Um
and just treating you well. So um
>> yeah be an example and pray.
>> All right.
>> And love each other.
>> Yeah. All right. Now, can we pray? Okay.
>> Heavenly Father, Lord, we thank you for
this question and answer session, Lord,
we thank you for so many visitors uh
that we have uh here today, Lord. And um
I just pray that you will continue to
bless this worship service. Help it to
be a blessing to all that are here now
and all that will hear it later. We ask
all these things in Jesus name. Amen. I
have one more thing to say. I'm glad our
team did not switch us. um was
um to our Catholic brother who's
visiting us for the first time. Can our
because you said to reach out to you,
but he doesn't have any way to do that.
So, I was wondering if our team could
either put my church email in the chat
or yours. Um because I don't Yeah. So,
can you guys do that for us so that he
can um so he can reach out to pastor? If
he send it if he sends me an email, I'll
just forward it to to pastor. So, yeah.
So, our Catholic brother who's visiting,
look out for that email. And if you need
if you would like to message the pastor,
you can do that. All right, continue to
worship with us. We will see you in the
divine worship service, don't go
anywhere.
Of
all the trees in the kingdom of the
plants, there's one that stands out from
all the rest. In some parts of the
world, this tree is venerated, even
worshiped as deity. In other parts of
the world, it is seen as a natural
jungle gym just waiting to be explored.
It is the home of many birds, a shade
for weary travelers, and a natural
playground for the children of men.
Of all the trees on God's green earth,
the mighty banyan is definitely one of
my favorites. Now, there are several
things that make this tree truly unique.
The bold banyan begins its life by
growing off of and deriving nutrients
from another tree. This tree is called
the host tree.
The mighty banyan sends down roots from
its branches all around the host tree.
Over time, it completely overtakes the
territory of the host tree and cuts off
its supply of sunlight. It's like the
banyan completely swallows up the host
tree, and the host tree forever becomes
a part of the banyan. Once the roots of
the banyan hit the soil and become well
grounded, it then grows into strong
trunk-like structures that support the
quickly extending branches of the
banyan, thus enabling the branches to
spread out far and wide. It looks like a
large system of multiple interlocking
trees, and yet it is only one singular
tree.
As I walked under the shade of the
mighty banyan and climbed upon its
sturdy branches, I couldn't help but
think of the many spiritual lessons this
tree teaches us. You see, the banyan is
able to live because of the host tree
that gave up its life. And just as the
host tree died so that the banyan tree
might live, so too, there is one that
died so that we might live forever.
Jesus died on the tree of the cross so
that we might have life everlasting. But
the banyan tree takes away life only to
give it back in rich fruit. So too, we
derive our life from our creator that we
might share it with those around us. And
once we are rooted and grounded in
Christ, we're then called to bear the
fruit of the spirit to the glory and the
honor of his name. The unique root
system of the banyan tree is also
reminded to us of the ultimate root,
Jesus. The book of Revelation calls him
the root of David, the bright and
morning star. Although the root is the
most unsightly part of the plant, it is
also the most powerful. It not only
sustains life by bringing nutrients to
the branches and leaves of the tree, but
it also holds up the massive weight of
the tree. Massive rocks and concrete
slabs are torn apart by the noless power
of the root. Hidden beneath the soil,
its power is mighty. And so too, the
power of the root of David hidden in the
heart can break the strongest bands of
sin. It is the root of David, Jesus
Christ, that gives us life and holds us
up as trees of righteousness. Like tree
roots, he's not always seen or noticed,
but surely he is there. And by the power
of that divine root, we shall be able to
withstand all the storms of the enemy.
For the Bible says that the root of the
righteous shall not be moved.
So today, I encourage you, let Christ be
the root and foundation of your life.
And as you do, you will become a
fruitbearing shelter in this unsafe and
starving world. A strong, solid, sturdy,
and stable sanctuary of refuge for
others. And with strong roots and sweet
fruits, you will be just like Jesus, who
sent his roots down from heaven to
earth, that we might be forever
connected, just like a heavenly banyan
tree to our wonderful God above.
We hope you've been blessed and inspired
by this new Reflections of Hope episode.
This episode is one of many that's been
produced all over the world. If you
haven't done so yet, please give our
video a like, share it with your
friends, and please follow us on
Instagram, Facebook, and YouTube. If
you'd like to see more inspiring
episodes and get access to much more
uplifting content, please go now to
patreon.com/revelationof
hope and sign up to be a member of our
Patreon page. Your monthly support will
not only give you early access to many
more inspiring videos, but it will also
enable us to continue to produce more of
these cinematic object lessons from
nature. Our goal is to produce and
release these episodes much more
frequently. So please prayerfully
consider partnering with us so that we
may continue to share the hope of Jesus
all over the world. Thank you so much
for your support. Aloha and Marin
Heat. Heat.
Heat. Heat. N.
Heat up
here.
Heat. Heat.
Welcome back, Living Mana Church family.
So good to have all of you here that are
your continuing to worship with us uh
today. We're so happy again to have you
here. I know we have many firsttime
people here today. So, welcome. And as
I'm going through these uh
announcements, I'll be able to tell you
a little bit more about Living Manage
Church and uh and that you will be able
to to find out uh more about us and and
different areas that you may want to
check out um and to see if it was is a
good fit or a blessing for you. Please
put in the chat where you are viewing
from. If you're just joining us for the
first time today, or if you didn't, put
in the chat where you're viewing from uh
during our first program, please do it
now so we can say a special welcome to
you. It's such a thrill uh to see where
so many people are worshiping from
today. We literally had so many people
from so many different countries. Um it
was just a blessing to see where
everybody's viewing from. So, if you're
just joining us or if you didn't do it
at that time, please do it now. And if
this is your first time, please put a
one in the chat. We want to say a very
special welcome to you. I don't know
about you, but I enjoy all the Sabbath
schools, but I really enjoy the question
and answers. It's so good to just answer
what's on your heart and interact with
you and be able to provide answers uh
from the word of God. And so um I know
that I enjoy answering the mental health
questions and I know my husband does for
the biblical questions as well. So,
blessings, Joy. You're viewing from
Barbados. Good to see you here. Welcome
uh to Living Mana Church. We also um
have um someone visiting from Lach,
Texas. Welcome. Good to see you here um
at Living Mana Church. We have Spring
Hill, Tennessee. Welcome to Living Mana
Church. Good to have you here with us
and worshiping with us today as well. We
have Dave from Barbados. Good to see
you, Dave. Uh we have quite a few that
worship with us from Barbados. Uh so
that's we have lots of people from the
the islands, Caribbean Islands. Uh but
Barbados, we seem to have a lot as well.
And Texas and um I said Texas and
Jamaica. That's what I meant to say. The
person that I was going to welcome to is
from Texas, but from Jamaica, we have a
lot. Um and all around the Caribbean
Islands. So we want to welcome. We have
someone from Texas. Welcome. Texas is a
big state. So, I don't know where you're
in Texas, but you're you're somewhere in
that big state. So, welcome to Living
Mana Church. Also, Queens, New York.
Good to see you here, uh, worshiping
with Living Mana. Uh, we have the
Bahamas. Welcome, beautiful uh, Bahamas.
Mario, I think, is here from the
Bahamas. Good to see you here. We have,
I think, Darl from New Mexico. Welcome.
Good to see you here at Living Mana. All
right. From Temple, Texas. That's where
you're you're visiting from. Good to see
you here at Living Mana Church. And we
have Houston, Texas. Welcome. Welcome.
It's good to see all of you here. Again,
if this is your first time, put a one in
the chat. But we thank you guys for
being here. Don't forget to like and
share and subscribe
uh to the YouTube channel that you are
on. Um our YouTube channel for our
church is uh my living mana. definitely
welcome people to uh welcome people and
invite people to church. Uh today we
also have someone from St. uh Benedict,
Pennsylvania. Welcome to Living Mana
Church. Good to see you here.
Shrivefeport uh Louisiana. That's where
my grandfather was was born and raised.
So welcome. Welcome here to Living Mana
Church. Uh we have uh Janice from Bise.
Good to see you here. Welcome to Living
Mana Church, everyone. Warsaw, New York.
Good to see you. All right. Looks like
our first timers were all in our earlier
service. Um, and everybody else has been
here for before. So, we're just glad to
see you guys back here worshiping with
Living Mana Church. Want to remind you
guys how you can stay connected to
Living Mana Church. If you are in North
America, you will be able to receive
text alert messages uh that will remind
you when we're going live. will also
provide other information to you and
announcements. Um, if you sign up for
text messages, so you can just text LMLC
to the 855 number there that you see on
your screen. You can also scan the Q QR
code and that will automatically sign
you up to get text alert messages from
Living Mana Church. It's so wonderful
and convenient to get text alerts
because we all know that life is busy.
will be in the middle of things. We will
think on Sabbath, hey, I'm going to make
sure that I do mental health Monday or
I'm going to go to true health Tuesday
or I want to make it for prayer meeting
to one of the services on Wednesday and
we forget. But if you sign up for the
LMLC text, you will be reminded you will
be reminded that we're going live in
about 20 minutes. And so you're also
able to get other information uh from
living mana church that um helps you to
just stay connected. If you are not in
North America and you are somewhere else
in the world where many of our viewing
audience and membership is in other
parts of the world, you need to sign up
for Mighty Networks and Mighty Networks
you'll see a link in the chat so that
you can sign up and that is our virtual
church home. So you will get information
tech um you'll get those alerts through
mighty networks and it's this is where
we form community uh because you get to
see all the small groups that we have
going on um you get to see the
leadership what they're doing you can
join them you make you make friends in
mighty networks you get to you get to
know people that are part of our living
uh mana community and so you have to
sign up for mighty networks because
you're you're going to want to do that
if you were here earlier the newsletter
will also So be on mighty networks and
there's so many other things. This is
where we do our afterlow after the
church service after Pastor Meyer's
sermon. We are all on mighty networks
and we get to share what we've learned,
our prayer request. Um just it's really
a blessing to get to know and to hear
everybody's voice on uh Mighty Networks
after uh the service is over today. So
you're going to definitely want to go to
that link and sign up for Mighty
Networks. Want to remind you guys that
we have LMOC kids. This is our
children's ministry part of living mana
church and we have great leadership
there and it's such a blessing for our
young people. They are having fun. It's
growing. They're learning so much. And
so if you would like one of if it's one
of your children or if you want to tell
somebody else that has children about
living mana kids, you can text kids to
855 that 2074107.
If you are out of the country, um you
can email LMOC kids at living.urch and
the leadership from LOC kids will get in
contact with you. If you need thinking
that you need to talk to Pastor Myers
and would like to meet with him, he does
have f virtual office hours. You can
email Patrice at living.live
and she will set up an appointment for
you.
wanting to just tell you guys about
Hangouts. And so we're going to show a
video at this time telling you a little
bit more about one of our ministries
called Hangouts. And that's what they
do. We hang out and have fun. So here's
a video that tells you a little bit more
about Hangouts.
>> Hello, I'm Ross.
>> And I'm Gina.
>> We're your hosts for Hangouts. Hangouts
happens here every other Sunday.
We get together on Zoom and we go into
small breakout rooms. The groups of 10
or less. Once you're in the breakout
room, then your hangout host will lead
you and the rest of the hangout crew in
trivia, ice breakers, and games
>> and much more. You know, we're here to
have fun. God has fun. He invented fun.
So come, let's have fun together with
our creator and enjoy time with each
other and with him. Thank you.
>> We're going to have a a good time
getting to know one another and everyone
is welcome. So bring a friend.
>> God bless.
All right. We also um want to tell you
about star um but I also want to let you
guys know that hangouts is a lot of fun.
So definitely uh take down the
information so you can be a part of the
next one. All right. So star our support
group is here to walk with you through
the journey of addiction recovery. Uh
whether you are just beginning or
continuing the path toward healing,
you're not alone. This is a safe,
judgmentfree space to share, grow, and
rebuild one step at a time. So, if
you're interested um in STAR, they are
now meeting on Thursday at 7:30 p.m.
Central time. Meetings are open to
everyone seeking support, encouragement,
and real connection. Come as you are.
Hope lives here.
Also want you guys to know about glow
groups. Glow groups are a small digital
gatherings where we have deep uh or we
dive deep, excuse me, into Pastor
Meyer's sermons and the word of God
together. These groups are designed for
real connection, thoughtful study, and
joyful fellowship. Members also begin
using photo theology chat GPT to play
Bible games and explore scripture in
fresh interactive ways. If you are
interested in joining or starting one of
these housefires, email group
livinga.urch.
Let's grow, glow, and go deeper
together. Sounds like a lot of fun.
Want you to know um about our about LMOC
teens. Friday Night Lights isn't a Bible
study. It's a movement led by teens for
teens. This is uh where creativity,
leadership, and faith uh collide. Expect
good energy, honest conversations, and a
space where you can grow without
pressure or judgment. If you know a teen
who's ready to tap into something real,
tell them to be there um on Zoom on
Friday nights uh Friday night lights.
And so there is um information there on
your screen where there's the email. I
want you to email if you have a teen or
if you're interested uh if you are a
teen and you'd like to uh get involved,
email LMLC teens living.urch.
Um they the leaders of LMLC teens did
ask me a few weeks ago to have you guys
um email them to let you know about what
time uh it's going to be. It's not
always on Friday, I don't believe
anymore, just because they have young
people from all around the world that
are are starting to wanting to join. And
so they are coming up with what time is
best for everyone. So definitely send an
email to that email that you see there
on your screen.
Want all the attent all the department
heads and ministry leaders. Uh we have
some information for you. So all right.
So it says don't forget your ministry
has the opportunity to be featured in
our 10-minute ministry spotlight during
Sabbath service. This is our moment to
share your mission, highlight what your
team does, and invite the church family
to get involved. You can choose one of
the one of two formats. You can do a
live interview like you saw today with
Sister Denise in the newsletter. Um, and
join us during the service for a short
conversation about your department. Um,
you can do a pre-recorded video, submit
a brief video introducing your ministry,
sharing updates, or inviting your
members and volunteers. This spotlight
is a powerful way to raise awareness
about your ministry, share upcoming
needs or initiatives, recruit new
members and volunteers, strengthen
connection across the LMLC community. If
your department hasn't signed up yet,
now is a perfect time. Let's make sure
every ministry has a chance to shine.
Contact GI Jones to sign up or learn
more about the exciting opportunity.
All right, do you guys remember weight
training? Um, well, weight training was
uh here at LOC. And if you've been
hearing about Adam Patel's amazing
classes uh for our El Moses or your or
you caught the buzz about Pastor
Ivorme's weight training, here's the
truth. This is one of the most
transformative trainings you'll find
anywhere, and it's available exclusively
through LOC. The full series is still
accessible on our YouTube playlist
featuring powerful guest teachers who
who brought their own depth and fire.
Adam Tel, Adam Patel, Dakota Day, Loami
Richardson, Calvin Kim. This isn't
generic evangelism content. This is
Alamosi crafted spiritual training
designed to teach you how to share your
faith with clarity and how to wait on
the Lord with purpose. If you've missed
it live, you can still tap in. If you
watched it once, it's worth watching
again. If you're if you're ready to
grow, this is where you start. We'll
drop the playlist link in the chat so
you can access the full experience only
here on LMC.
All right, guys. Volunteers are still
needed. Are you ready to serve? We got
open doors and open uh rolls. Head to
the service opportunity section in
Mighty Networks to see where your gifts
can make a difference. Right now, we're
especially looking for help with Elos
Kids. Our children ministry is
especially in need of volunteers to
support administrative roles and small
behindthecenes tasks that make a big
impact. Not every role requires a large
time commitment or extensive onboarding.
your commitment or extensive onboarding
um experience, your willingness alone
goes a long way. And the benevolence
committee is also looking for
volunteers. We're looking uh for
compassionate, dependable volunteers to
help review requests, coordinate,
support, and serve our community with
care. All right, Globe Groups. Uh we
mentioned earlier that our digital small
groups are growing and we need more host
to help create welcoming space for
connection and disciplehip. Whether you
love welcoming people, organizing behind
the scenes, crafting messages, or
working uh with tech, we've got a spot
for you. Let's build together. Let's
serve together. Remember to check out
all the volunteer opportunities on
service section of Mighty Networks and
it's updated weekly.
So that if you fit in any of those
roles, please uh go and check that out.
All right, want to remind you guys about
AlamoC Global. As you guys know, if
you've been here uh with us, you know
that we are a global online church and
we are going into all of the world. Uh
right now, we're broadcast all around
the world, but we want to speak the
languages of the world. And right now
we're going in seven different
languages, but we want to go into more.
And so for those of you who are just
joining us for the first time, we want
to show you what LMC Global is all
about.
Fore!
Foreign! Foreign!
foreign.
Let's keep LMLC Global in our prayers.
Um, and I'm in a moment I'm just about
to show you or tell you how you can
continue to support LMLC global so that
we can continue to go into all the world
um and um in the future go into more
languages of the world than just seven.
And there's a question in the chat.
Someone's asking uh do you have to be a
member to volunteer?
No, you don't. If you are a viewing
audience and you would like to help, uh
you will um obviously go through a
process to be able to help and
volunteer, but we uh welcome your
participation and wanting to uh start
helping with Loc.
So, to let you guys know how you can uh
support Locosc Global, you can do that
by going to adventistgiving.org.
here is where you will be able to give
your tithe and your offering to support
all that we do here at LMLC um LLC
church. And so a virtual tithe envelope
will fall down when you put in Living
Mana uh Church. We are a church that's a
part of the Northeastern Conference. So
you can give your tithe and again that
will go to the Northeastern Conference.
And then when you want to support living
mana church and to help us to do all the
things that we do with living mana
church you would give to the local
church budget. So you can give your
offering uh there you will also see a
line where you can help with the
benevolence fund where pe when people
are in need of assistance and they are
asking uh living mana church to help if
we are able to help them it's going to
come for from the benevolence fund. So
if you would like to give to uh that uh
area and part of our ministry here at
Living Mana, you can give to that and
that will help us to be able to help
others. If you um do not want to give
virtually online, you can send in your
tithe offering and offering to Living
Manage Church. the address that you see
there on the screen, PO Box 428, Owens
Crossroads, Alabama 35763,
and you will be able to mail in your
tithe and offering. Please put in a
little note uh with your with your tithe
and offering to let us know what is for
tithe, what is for offering or even
another area uh that you see there on
the tithe envelope that you want your
funds to go and to support so we know
where to allocate those funds um and so
that we can put it in the right place
where you're wanting to put uh and to
give. So those are the ways that you can
give to support Living Mana Church. Just
want to say thank you to all of you that
have been with Living Mana Church. Um
we've almost been here four years, guys.
It's February 7th today and in April
9th, it is our fourth uh anniversary of
Living Mana Church. And so we are so
thankful for all of you who have been
supporting Living Mana Church by your
presence, by sharing with people,
telling them all about it, inviting them
to different programs, uh, to church
service and programs that we do during
the week, inviting them to mental health
Monday, true health Tuesday, and the two
prayer services that we have, uh, during
the middle of the week as well. And you
guys do that. you invite people and tell
them and we are just so very thankful
for your prayers and for your financial
gifts that help keep Living Mana Church
up and running. So, thank you to all of
you. And right now, we just want to
praise God. We just want to thank him
for his faithfulness and what he does
for each and every one of us. So, if you
would please join me uh as we just bow
our heads in prayer.
Heavenly Father, Lord, I thank you uh
just for the Sabbath. Lord, I'm thank so
thankful for the Sabbath to worship you,
to give praise to you, Lord, and just to
spend time together with our lovely
church members that are literally all
around the world. It is a blessing that
you have allowed us to be a church in
this space where so many people are on
YouTube, they're online, they're on
Facebook, they're on social media, and
you have allowed us to plant a church
right where they are. And we praise you
for that. We thank you, Lord. Lord, I
just want to lift up everyone that is
hearing my voice, th those who are live
right now and those that will hear and
watch later on. Lord, you know all the
different things. You know their
praises, Lord. You know their burdens.
You know the request. You know what's on
their heart. Lord, there's marriages
that are struggling. I ask that you help
them. There are parents that are
struggling and connecting with their
children, their teenage children, their
young adult children. Lord, even their
grandchildren sometimes. So, I pray for
them, Lord. Lord, there's people there's
those here that are physically having
physical illness, Lord, and they're
needing healing. We pray healing upon
all that are sick. And Lord, finances
are an issue um in this economy, in this
world that we're living in. So many
people are going through so many
different things. Lord, I pray that you
will bless them financially. those who
are needing a financial blessing when
they are just worried that the lights
may be turned off or whatever the case
may be. Lord, send send them the funds
that they need so that doesn't happen.
But Lord, give them peace as they are
going through that and let them know
that you are with them. You are always
with them in every trial and every
tribulation. Lord, I pray for Pastor
Meyers for the message that you have put
on his heart. I pray that he will that
he will deliver it in the way that you
want him to deliver it so that it will
bless our hearts and change our lives.
Lord, I ask all these things in Jesus
name. Amen.
Let him use you. That phrase is a common
refrain in the black church, often
lifted in a shout towards the minister
of the moment.
Let him use you. And by God's grace,
they did. Let him use you as he used
Rosa Parks, whose peaceful resistance
set in motion one of the largest social
movements in history. And as he used
Pastor Ralph Abernathy, who soon after
organized the Montgomery bus boycott,
helping to bring bus segregation to an
end. Let him use you as he used Dorothy
Cotton and Septima Clark who empowered a
generation of voters through the
citizenship education program. And as he
used Pastor Frederick Douglas Ree whose
work in Alabama led to the passage of
the Voting Rights Act. Let him use you.
As he used Dorothy Height, whose
leadership in the Civil Rights Movement
for the first time gave a voice to the
issues affecting AfricanAmerican women.
as he used John Lewis who fought
tirelessly to end segregation and
courageously marched from Selma to
Montgomery. Let him use you as he used
Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. who dedicated
his life to achieving equality and
justice for every American. Let him use
you. They did and history was made. And
today, even now, you can almost hear
them joining with that great cloud of
witnesses, exhorting you and me right
now to let him use you.
I
will
lift up mine eyes to the heels.
From whence cometh my help,
my help cometh from
the Lord.
The Lord which made heaven and earth.
He
said
he will not suffer thy foot
thy foot to be moved.
The Lord which keep
not slumber
sleep
for
the
Lord is thy keeper.
The Lord is thy shame.
upon
thy
right hand.
Upon
thy right hand.
No,
the sun shall not smite thee by day or
the moon by night.
He shall preserve thy soul
even forever
more.
My
help.
My help.
All of my help cometh from
the
Lord.
Here at Living Mana, we bear each
other's burdens.
When you need support or prayer, when
you're feeling discouraged
or alone or anxious,
you don't have to face life struggles
alone.
Let us come boldly unto the throne of
grace that we may obtain mercy and find
grace to help in our time of need.
The Lord is close to the brokenhearted
and saves those who are crushed in
spirit.
Nothing.
Amen. Amen. Greetings saints of the most
high God and our beautiful living man of
family worldwide. Welcome to another
edition of living manners prayer and
praise time. I am brother Terry here
with my lovely bride Amra. As always we
are happy and excited to be able to
serve you in this capacity. What a what
a wonderful day it is to worship the
Lord no matter what's going on. Can we
say amen?
>> And listen, you know, saints, we greet
you and today you you heard me say uh uh
welcome to our living man of family
worldwide. We're not just saying that.
Listen,
>> we have seen folk today. We're seeing
you in the chat. Love all of you.
Listen, we're going to do a different
little roll call today because, you
know, I've been doing this a while, but
today it just seems like the term
worldwide and living man of global just
took on a whole new uh uh uh uh meaning
today. I mean, the same meaning. We're
always out there grow global and
worldwide, but we want to be aware of
this thing. I saw people from Australia,
Ethiopia, Greece, I mean
>> Caribbean,
>> the Caribbean was here, South Dakota was
here, China, France, interacted with
these people. There's not just we're not
just calling off lovely sounding, you
know, names of countries and states, but
I saw the names of people and I tried to
reach out to everybody. Um, South
Dakota, like I said, southern Ohio,
Jamaica, New York, and Texas are here.
Long Beach in the house, Mexico, love
y'all. Oklahoma, obviously Trinidad and
Tobago, the Dutch Caribbean, we always
got to remember you. Uh, brother Elco,
we know I saw somebody from San Jose,
Kenya, Zambia, Bise, definitely
Barbados, the Bahamas, Palao is in the
house. And Louisiana, all right,
Louisiana, we know y'all here. Love
y'all. And beautiful Jamaica. Just
everywhere. And and and so if you're
watching from these beautiful places, we
want to send our love out to you and
thank God for this amazing family. Truly
a global family. And it it makes us
really think we got to start thinking
global in everything we do and living
global and and praying globally and
serving globally, loving globally. We
want to circle the globe. Amen. I see
you. That's right. We are definitely
global. And so, you know, we got a
message that God has sent to the world.
And so, wherever you are, beloved, let's
join our hearts. Let's join our our
minds and our spirits. Spamco, I see you
there, brother. I see you there over
there in Europe. And so, God bless you.
I forgot that prayer request. We prayed
on Power Wednesday. We're going to be
able to connect. But listen, I want to
Felis Sabado Familia. Yes, Sister
Annette. Love you. I did shout out
Mexico. Good to see you there. And uh so
listen, here's a scripture we're all
familiar with. I've been quoting it a
bit. 1 Corinthians chapter 13:10 says,
"There hath no temptation taken you, but
such as is common to man."
>> But God is faithful, who will not suffer
you to be tempted above that which you
are able, but will with the temptation
also make a way of escape that you might
be able to bury. I mean, something
really awesome about that occurred to me
today. Um, you know, I can remember a
time when I was in the middle of a big
mess. Y'all heard me talk about a
thousand times. I'm gonna keep talking
about it. That's my testimony. In the
middle of the mess, I was watching
Pastor Iva Meyer, right? And I remember
praying about wanting to go to Bible
school and wanting to graduate seminary.
And I did, you know, graduate uh
seminary, not an physics seminary, by
the way, which we've told a thousand
times and um fought and argued with my
professors and everything. But but while
I was there, I was watching Iva Meyer. I
never really realized that I would get
out one day and sit under this amazing
ministry. And God showed me something
that he's given us. Really last night,
it came to fruition like exploded in my
mind. and I've already been aware of it,
but it's like he took another layer of
of uh uh uh just added another layer of
blessing to it. We have a prophecy
curriculum here at Living Man. Pastor
Meer has back to basics, Matthew 24, the
elephant in the room, right? We just
went over the story of the 10 horns. I'm
going to tell you something, saints.
Listen to me. Binge watch all of that.
God has given us an amazing prophetic
curriculum for his people for this hour.
And the reason why I keep emphasizing
that is because I mean, you ever
wondered what was taught to the school
of the prophets? What were they teaching
them in there? You know, I don't know.
But I know God has given us a word
that's relevant for this hour. And these
teaching, these distinctive prophetic
teachings are what makes us who we are
in this hour. We are the remnant. We are
God's people. This is indeed our finest
hour. But what a wonderful thing that
God has given us a word that allows us
to have answers to know what's going on.
And here, let me say this and I can shut
up because I not I pastor going to
preach in a minute. All right? But
here's something for you. Listen,
if you ever wonder why is there so many
distractions? Why is there so much mess
going on? one thing going on here at
work or at home in our marriages, in our
health, in our finances, always
something. It's because it's it's it's
all designed really to either deepen us
in the Lord or to get us away from this
incredible message God has given us to
distract us from that study time and
that prayer time and staying focused on
this word. Do not allow life's trials
and struggles to snatch this amazing
prophetic word from your heart and mind.
Beloved brothers and sisters, this is
indeed our finest hour. So I want to
encourage you, stand and be strong in
the Lord, and the power of his might.
Put on the whole armor of God that you
might be able to stand against the ws of
the devil. He gonna keep on coming. He
gonna keep coming, but the victory is
already secure in Jesus. Can we say
amen?
>> Amen to that.
>> All right. All right. Love everybody.
Don't have time for a roll call today,
but we do have something special for
you. Now, my beloved bride is going to
tell us what God has been doing in the
lives of his people. Yes. Before that, I
have some announcements as usual.
If you have a prayer request or a praise
report that you would like to submit um
to the prayer team, please send an email
to pray
living
people to join us. It is a very robust
and active community.
um you would never regret it. It is uh
we have so many different things going
on that we need people to help with. So
please also send an email to pray at
living mana.urch if you have an interest
in joining us in the prayer team. If you
need a special ops
uh team and you're requesting a special
ops team for yourself or a loved one,
please send an email to spec ops at
livingmana.urch.
If you need a midweek pickup, please
join us every Wednesday at Power
Wednesday. that is at 4:30 p.m. Pacific
Standard Time, 6:30 Central, 7:30
Eastern Standard Time. And it is an
amazing um weekly program where we
switch off doing testimonies and
devotionals.
We have um active prayer and fellowship.
So, it is a perfect time to come um
pray. Following that, we have our weekly
power line. That is the live prayer that
happens um we take in the chat. That's
every Wednesday at 6:00 pm Pacific
Standard Time, 900 PM Eastern. And that
takes place on YouTube um on uh the LMC
website or YouTube channel as well as
Power of the Lamb. So come join us
directly following power Wednesday for
live prayer.
If you would like to join the women's
ministry on mighty networks, please send
an email to women
living.urch.
Um I think it's so important for women
and men to join women and men's groups
here and be an active part of the
community. Um, if you are a man, please
send an email to menlivingmana.urch
to get involved in the men's group where
you can
just connect on all of the issues and
um, special needs that men go through.
Um, what a great way for men to connect
in our church.
>> All right, that is the weekly
announcements. Um, one thing about the
men's group, men's ministry, uh,
First Lady and Dr. Ricardo White have
been doing a series on men's mental
health on mental health Monday and I'm
sure you probably heard the announcement
and some of you men may not have been
able to be there. Um, but there have
been a lot of questions and they've been
touching on a lot of very powerful
topics and and if you if you haven't
been able to show up or you feel like
maybe there was a point or a topic that
needed more time spent with the Lord
laid it on my heart to take uh make a
list of the questions that they've gone
over, maybe go through back through and
listen again and jot those down and I
want to submit those to brother Elco
leader of the men's ministry and him
along with uh brother Kashif and brother
um Kirk and and brother Ross and maybe
they can put those together and figure
out a way to incorporate them into their
meetings so we can have more discussions
and address those topics more because
some of those topics I found to be very
very very important and instrumental in
my own u mental health. So, uh,
>> yes, and they are still in the midst of
the men's
>> series that they're doing on Mental
Health Monday, and they're recorded. So,
if you are interested in going back,
it's also for women as well, so we know
how to support our men in our world.
All right, praise reports.
First one coming from Lisa Clark. Praise
God. God for receiving a grant for
textbooks this semester. Practically all
my material costs were covered.
>> Amen. Amen.
From Jamie A. The first one was from
last week caught in the chat. Praise God
for getting mom safely through a
threehour oral surgery.
>> Amen. And from today, praise God, our
neighbor who had open heart surgery
Christmas Eve is celebrating his
birthday today. He's home and healing.
>> Praise God.
>> Amen. From Olive Torres.
Celebration is in order. A few days ago,
I requested prayer for this couple, and
you are the epitome of how prayer can
make a difference. My dearly beloved,
God truly is faithful. Here's the praise
report from my friend Meline and her
husband Boy. FYI, Boy passed his
adjustment of status interview. He's now
a permanent resident. Praise the Lord.
Thank you all for your intercessory
prayers. They are extending their
warmest thanks.
>> Amen.
From Pauline Goodine.
Love you Pauline.
Hallelujah. Praise the Lord. I filed my
case. Glory to God. God's timing is the
best timing. Now, let his will be done.
Glory.
>> Amen.
>> And we will be continuing to pray over
that case, Pauline. But we are glad that
it is the time is here.
>> Amen.
>> And finally, from Jesse Fostino, praise
report. A brother from my local church
was about to be evicted. I don't have
all the details, but I know God helped
him out through his servants. His rent
was paid and groceries were taken care
of.
>> Praise God.
>> And praise God for young brother Jesse
Ostino. Jesse, you continue to be an
inspiration to us all. We love you here
and thank you for allowing us to share
your life with you. Also, Sister Jod, I
saw your message in the chat. I left you
a message in Slack, sister, so uh we can
make that appointment. And uh God bless
everybody. Love y'all. You know,
February uh is the month of love. I
mean, God's people every every day is
love for us, but February is, you know,
it's the the month of romance.
Everybody's kind of sharing their
Valentine's and all that different
stuff. But
>> I mean, our anniversary is this month,
too.
>> Our anniversary is this month on the
20th. Believe me, I did not forget that.
And uh I have a birthday coming up by
the grace of God. Um, I will be turning
60 here in a couple of weeks.
>> Milestone birthday.
>> So, thank you.
>> On the 26th.
>> Amen. Praise God for that. And any the
rest of you are celebrating birthdays in
February. We love you and we are
celebrating your beautiful life. Thank
God for you uh and for allowing us to uh
experience you while we are here
together in Earth's history. Now, but
here's something really special that's
going to happen in the month of
February. Uh, one of our special ops
teams is going to be doing intercessory
prayer throughout the whole month of
February. In fact, it is Papa Ronnies,
Pastor Myers's father. His special ops
team, the Fab Seven, as they are called,
are going to be coming on with us. And
so, we're really excited about them.
I've had a chance to pray with these
sisters. I mean, these sisters really
are I mean, they're specifically
assigned to Papa Ronnie, but when they
start praying, they're praying for
everybody. I believe I've been there.
And so, I've had them in my ear at work
and just listening to them and um
uh wow. Let me tell you, who is this?
Someone said Scarlet turned 62
days ago.
>> No, no, no.
>> Oh, Scarlet.
>> Crystal. Chris said, "Scarlet turned six
>> two days ago." Well, listen. Happy
birthday, Scarlet. Wow. Young Scarlet is
just growing up, ain't she?
>> And SP,
my baby was born this month.
>> Amen. Amen. I just happened to look down
and see that. And hello, Sister.
>> Happy early birthday anniversary. Okay.
You know what? We didn't mean to start
another roll call. That's not why while
we're here. So, go ahead. I don't mind
it though because I was watching pastor.
Those are our pastors, right? And we we
we follow the example. I love the way
they intimately interact and and and
it's not just like pastor said, it's not
just a production. It is, but it's not.
We're family. It's church. We interact.
We lean on we love one another. We
fellowship. We support. It's real, you
know.
>> It's real. And I I I'm want to follow
that example. I like that. I like that.
It's beautiful. So yeah, we reaching out
to family. You know, we're here and uh
I'm glad you mentioned that, Crystal.
And we miss you, too. Love you.
All right. So, what were we talking
about? Oh, we're talking about the Fab 7
getting ready to come on. So, today I
think we're going to have Sister Barbara
Simmons, Sister Birdie, who's telling
me, and we're going to have Sister
Christina, and they're going to come on
and they're going to lead us to the
throne of grace. So, we're we're excited
to have them. Again, they're Papa
Special Ops team. They'll be here for
the whole month. and uh get to be
blessed by them.
>> Amen.
>> So, my sisters, bless you as you come.
Believe they should be coming up here
shortly.
And we want to thank you all for praying
for our our technical team and and
behind the scenes. They do a wonderful
job.
>> Hi, Barbara.
>> There she is. Sister Barbara.
>> Hello.
>> Can you hear me?
>> Hi. God bless you.
>> Yes ma'am. you can.
>> Okay. I'm not sure about the other two.
Um
maybe we'll just wait a minute and see
if they come on.
>> All right. So, maybe in the meantime,
you can introduce yourself briefly as we
wait for them. There they go.
>> There's TMA.
>> Yeah.
>> Praise the Lord.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah.
Oh, we can't hear you, TMA.
>> Okay,
>> TMA, we can see you, but we can't hear
you.
>> Okay, Sister Barbara, you may want to go
ahead and start and uh she she'll jump
in.
>> Yes. Because I have a little bit of
introduction here uh to tell you about
the Fab 7. Um, like like brother Terry
told you, we are Papa Ronnie special ops
team. And for those of you who are new
to us today or just visiting, a special
ops team is a prayer team that what
pastor calls do sniper prayer.
That means that we um we we hone right
in on our target for praying. And this
team meets three days a week to pray for
Paparani, but we also pray for other
people too. Um, but on the Fab 7, there
are seven of us. And um, there is
Birdie, there is Christina,
there is Chalala, and there is Marcella
and Joanne and Simone, and myself. And
we're all in different locations.
Um the furthest away is Chalala. She's
in Zambia
and um I am in um on the island of
Anguila
and um Birdie is in Connecticut,
Christina is in Colorado.
Marisella is in Kansas.
Joanne is in Trinidad.
And Joanne is our coach.
And um and like I said, we get together
three times a week
and uh pray for Paparani. Plus, we we
pray for the Meyers family. We pray for
um the Fab 7. We pay pray for the prayer
list. We pray for um
um various. We pray for Sister Stacy. we
pray for um
um I forget any more that we pray for
but it it's a lot. So um today we are
going to do intercessory prayer and when
I first came to um when I first came to
the special ops team I didn't hardly
even know what intercessory prayer was.
I came from originally from a different
religion and um and We never prayed. So
I didn't know how. That's why I joined
the prayer team so I could learn how to
pray.
>> So let me read to you this the um
the scripture that Chris Sister
Christina researched for us about
intercessory prayer. So I am reading
first Timothy 2 verse 1 and two and it
says therefore I exhort first of all
that supplication prayers intercessions
and giving of thanks be made for all men
for kings and all who are in authority
that we may lead a quiet life, a quiet
and peaceable ible life in all godliness
and reverence. So it tells us in
scripture to pray for others.
Okay, it looks like Christina is still
having trouble or not Christina but but
B. But
um I am going to go down through the
prayer list
and hopefully by the time I am down
through the prayer list um
she will be able to do the actual
prayer. And I just wanted to let
everybody know that the prayers that are
not mentioned today will be prayed over
by the prayer team. We collect all of
the prayers. They go to the prayer team
and um and they are prayed over and
prayed over and prayed over. They're
prayed over until you tell us that they
have been
um answered. So, just want to let you
know that if you don't hear your prayer
today, it will be prayed. So, first of
all, we have an urgent request for
special circumstances
for encouragement
and a reminder
that this special person is a child of
God and that he loves you and that God
loves you.
And Llaya Peterson is asking for prayer
for their February 14th ministry when
they'll be handing out crocheted hearts
in a gift bag with a great controversy
at their local church.
And blessing Joy is asking for a miracle
for Doug to touch his heart and allow
him to understand your love, God.
Um, and she is asking, "Please save his
soul by any means. Comfort him at this
time." And Laya Peterson is is asking
for prayer for her sister, Dawn. She
says, "Thank you that she is out of the
hospital, but is still plagued by
medical issues. Pray for healing for
Dawn."
And Christy 5791 is asking for prayer
for Lewis Torado,
her neighbor who's having serious health
problems and is temporarily blind as
she's asking for his sight to be
restored and his health to be improved.
And
Adega Havammani
is asking for continued prayer for his
family in Iran who are under
unimaginable
continued danger and darkness. He says,
"Please don't forget them." And we
won't. We won't forget them. We'll
continue to pray for them.
And Christy 5791
asks is asking for prayer for her sons
and for the rest of her family,
brothers, sisters, nieces, nephews, and
all of her friends.
And I am Rain is asking for prayer for
her son Caleb's mom who is in the
hospital with a life-threatening
situation.
She says he she asks for prayer for
family and for God's healing.
>> Um we are all asking you to pray for all
our children. Give them spiritual
guidance and put the Holy Spirit in
them.
And Josie Lenora 9035
is asking you to is asking for prayer to
heal the rift between her and her
brothers.
Brother Terry, our our beloved brother
Terry who is the head of our prayer team
and leads us every day. He is asking for
prayer. He's in New York City and he's
asking for prayer for
strength and endurance and patience as
he is care in New York City pray caring
for his bed bound sister. He says it's
not easy. So we ask you Lord for
strength and endurance and patience for
him.
And we ask and we
and Ponzi pansy keep we is asking for
prayer to keep him and his family in
prayer especially his son Moansa and
friend Gray and Black Rob 9479
is asking for pray prayer for results of
his nerve conduction study that it will
be favorable
and Landre
485 Five is asking for continued
protection and guidance and and
employment.
And I think our sister Birdie is back on
now. Thank you. Thank you, Lord. And she
will be praying over all of these
prayers that we just read out to you.
Can you guys hear me?
>> No, we
>> There you are.
>> There you are. Yes, we can.
>> I'm good.
>> Praise the Lord.
>> Are you good?
>> Praise the Lord. Praise Praise the Lord.
Praise the Lord. Happy Sabbath, my
brothers and sisters. Manner, to God be
the glory. Great things you have done.
God is great and God is good and God is
marvelous and we just want to give God
thanks and praise for this another
beautiful and blessed Sabbath day of
rest. Thankful for my dear sister
Barbara. She already read all the prayer
requests from the chats which I'm going
to cover and whatever is not covered at
this moment you can have sure that it's
covered right during the course of the
week. My brothers and sisters who always
place their prayer requests and trust us
to lift them up to the throne room of
God's grace and mercy. So right during
the course of the week, we cover you
guys with your prayer requests and we
give you thanks and praise. So let's
pray. Heavenly Father, thank you again
today for this beautiful Sabbath day of
rest. Thank you for your grace and thank
you for your mercy, oh God. Thank you
that you have spear our life to see this
another beautiful, beautiful day. In
fact, that we are here, it's a lot of
blessing because so many have laid their
head to rest last night. Did not wake up
this morning. But you allow us another
day, another moment right here on planet
earth where we can just give you all the
praise and all the glory and all the
honor. It does not belongs to us God. It
belongs to you. Everything's belongs to
you. Whatever we do here on planet earth
is all about our Lord and Savior Jesus
Christ. It's about to bring us home back
into the beautiful garden, the beautiful
home that he has gone to prepare for
each and every one of us. And he wants
to make sure that we as his sons and
daughter, his children make it back
home. And we have to do our part amidst
everything that we are facing right here
on planet earth. All the different
trials. We have to keep our eyes focus
upon the goal. And our goal supposed to
be going back home which is heaven.
While we are living here on planet
earth, we are going through a journey.
We are traveling on a train journey and
the final destination is heaven. And we
do not need to miss out on this
beautiful, beautiful, glorious moment in
heaven. What a day that will be when we
shall see our Lord and Savior Jesus
Christ face to face. And today I want to
lift up all these beautiful prayer
wicked cresses that sister Barbara
already called out. And there are so
many of them, oh father. Some are
suffering from physical sickness.
Father, those who are suffering from
sickness physically hitting their body,
their joints, whether it's cancer,
diabetes, arthritis, whatever sickness
they may be going through at this
moment, they can have assurance that
Jesus Christ, the great healer, the
great physician is right there. He will
never leave them and he will never
forsake them. Under no situation and
under no circumstances, he is always
right there. So as we lift up everyone
who are suffering in the physical rims
of their system of their body right now,
I continue to plead the cleansing blood
of Jesus, the great healer, to fill
them, to wash them, to cleanse them, to
purify them from the crown of their head
to the sole of their feet and night
them. I pray that the Holy Spirit will
continue to tabernacle with them. And I
pray that they will never give up hope.
Whatever they are facing, they will
never give up hope. There are some who
may be struggling financially. There are
some who may be struggling and family
part. Whatever they are struggling with,
I lay you all at the foot of Jesus
Christ. Wrapped up in the palm of his
hands right now. Those big agape arms of
our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ. Wrap
them tightly around your sons and your
daughter of a father in the name of
Jesus Christ. I curse and rebuke every
dynamic forces that may try to attack
them in the name of Jesus. remove,
annihilate and uprooted from them so
that they will keep their high focus and
be strengthened as they continue to
journey in through this planet earth
that we are traveling on at this moment.
Those who are suffering and need more
spiritual help. I pray that the
cleansing blood of Jesus, the Holy
Spirit will tabernacle with them. Wrap
his arms around them. Breathe your Holy
Spirit upon them from the crown of their
head and to the sole of their feet so
that whatever they faces, they will
remember that they serve a true and
living God, the God of our forefather,
Abraham, Isaac, Jacob, Shedrach, Mitch
of Abedo. And they cannot give up. They
cannot let go. They must keep their high
focus. Our goal, our destination is
heaven. and let us allow nothing to
separate us from such a beautiful
beautiful place where our God is
preparing for us. There are some who are
suffering from mental, emotional and a
lot of personal issues that we don't
know but God knows everything because
nothing is hidden from God and I claim
you all in the name of Jesus Christ. I
claim your heart to God because God want
us to be heart ready every step, every
journey of this place where we are
traveling on planet earth. So whatever
the issue you are going through at this
moment have a faith in God. Trust in him
because God said in his word even before
we open up our mouth and utter anything
before him that he already hear that he
already answer. And when we pray when we
as brothers and sister intercede and
come to gather the faith the prayer of
the faithful reach into the throne room
of God's grace and mercy and the
blessing come flowing down upon every
individual. There are angel who are
ascending and descending back and forth
from heaven back and forth upon that
leather picking up our prayer request is
when we lay them down and he bring them
back up into the throne room of God's
grace and mercy. God send out the
blessing at this moment oh God pour out
your blessing because if ever a people
your sons and your daughter and planet
earth need a blessing. It is no other
time than this very special time. We are
living in the final moment on planet
earth. Yet we know not the time or the
moment when you shall put in your
appearance. But we know this is judgment
time. This is end time we are living in.
And we need to keep our high focus. We
need to pray like we have never prayed
before. We need to cover each other with
the cleansing blood of Jesus. We need to
plead for the outpouring of the Holy
Spirit to wash us, to cleanse us, to
fill us like on the day of Pentecost. So
nothing would be withhold from us. So we
will not be afraid of nothing that may
come in our way. Because we serve a
mighty God who promises as David said in
his word, I was young and now I'm whole.
Never ever yet have I seen the righteous
forsaken are their seed begging bread.
And according to your word, oh God, your
promises that you will supply our daily
needs, according to your riches in
glory, and your riches in glory is
everything. And it's from that resources
that you pour out and supply the needs.
Everyone that have a needs today,
whatever it is, personal, spiritual,
physical, emotionally, and all had a
aspect of your life, lay them at the
foot of Jesus Christ night and day.
Continue to trust, continue never to
give up, continue to push your requests
to God because we cannot bear um weary
out God under no situation. We cannot
weary him. Burdens are lifting at
Calvary and Jesus is very near and we
need to continue lifting up our burden.
We need to continue crying out to God
for our brothers and sister who are
suffering who are struggling across the
world in every situation that they faces
at this moment and living mana platform
church here it is a online church that
goes across the globe all over the
world. So there are brothers and sisters
in the four quarters of the world who
are a part of living mana church and
they faces different struggle in their
own part of vineyard that they are
living in and we continue to lay them in
God hands and continue to ask God to
breathe your holy spirit upon them that
they will never ever let go of your
hands because you God will never let go
of any of us as your sons and your
daughter. We continue to lift up sister
Eden aba father. You know exactly who
sister Eden is at this very present
moment and time and I want to lay your
daughter in the hollow palm of your
hands. You know where she is right now.
I pray oh God that your cleansing blood
will wrapped around her. I pray that you
will dispatch holy angels from heaven
and encircle around your dear daughter
sister Eden by name and by number.
Because you know what? Not a strong of
her here is missing. You know her. your
farmer in the womb of her mother. You
created her. You have a plan and a
purpose for her. The devil is trying to
attack her. But in the mighty name of
Jesus, and this your holy Sabbath day of
rest, I annihilate and curse every
dynamic forces away from your dear
daughter, sister Eden, right now. Wrap
her up right now in the hollow palm of
your hands. Bring her comfort. Bring the
parents comfort at this moment, ab
father, and the rest remaining family
along with us as the living mana
platform family who continue to lay her
in the hollow palm of your hands. And we
will not stop crying and praying out for
Eden and call her name into the hands of
God because we know that the devil
cannot win under no situation and
circumstances. So I pray God right now
bring comfort to heathen. Whatever her
struggle, whatever her trials, whatever
her situation, we lay it all in the palm
of your hands. We all come in oneness in
agreement as we cover sister Eden this
day and constantly and continually. We
continue to thank you for the all the
tech teams and the equipments father
that you uses to take care of this
beautiful living mana platform across
the globe. Father, what a beautiful
thing it is where your sons and your
daughters from different part of the
vineyard can come together and yet be
such as such a beautiful thing as the
tech team because they serve behind the
scene. Oh God, so touch them from the
crown of their head to the sole of their
feet. Not only this moment but for the
rest remaining of their life. Touch
their family. They're going out and
they're coming in wherever they may be.
I pray in the mighty name of Jesus. be
with all the equipments that serve in
this beautiful online churches not only
for today but for every day because this
church is a 24hour around the clock.
There is always something going on and
we give you thanks and praises for your
goodness and for your mercy. The hearway
is a wide open space and God provide
this beautiful airway and using it to
draw his sons and daughter into the
kingdom of heaven. While we are still
living here in the kingdom of grace that
he came to set up, he want us to make
sure that our life is right with him. So
that when he shall come in the clouds of
glory to bring home his chosen rooster
of saints, all of us who have make our
calling and election sure, we'll be
going home, riding back home. If we are
resting, we'll be in the first
resurrection. And if we're awake, we
will all caught up together to meet our
Lord and Savior in the sky. We pray
above father for our dear pastor pastor
Hiver Meyers at this very special moment
in time. You have a special word for
your sons, for your daughters across the
globe at this moment. Oh God, all his
words are from you. You have called him.
You have appointed him. You have
anointed him. And you are using him in
such a way in such a time as this
father. You are using him to spread your
good word, the gospel of aa father
across the world to bring your sons and
daughter back into your fold of aa
father whom the devil is trying to rip
away. But God you will not allow that to
happen. So I pray oh God that the words
today from pastor Hiver Myers touch him
from the crown of his head to the sole
of his feet. Touch his mic. Touch his
gadget. Touch his studio room father
that he's using at this moment. anoint
it. Hedge him around father in every
direction from A to Z. Oh aba father
wherever he may be not only at this
moment but for the rest remaining of his
life whether by here here or flying over
father I pray that you will continue to
cover pastor Hiver Meyers in every
direction and his family father his
beautiful wife and all of the other
remaining of the meers family at this
moment. So we thank you for the living
manner that we are about to participate
in. the living manner that is here to
fill us for the rest remaining of this
day and for the rest remaining of this
week father something for us to look to
to reflect upon father touch him with
every touch of yours aba father and
continue to be with pastor hivyers be
with the sermon aba father and we thank
you for this beautiful living word aba
father that we will all participate in
at this very present moment and time you
are a powerful god who promised never to
leave us and never to forsake take us
and we are so grateful for your
goodness, for your mercy that flows
around our life, Aba Father. And when
all is said and done, I pray that all of
us will make it home into that beautiful
and glorious kingdom that we will never
never depart from you again. What a
beautiful moment that will be when there
will be no more sickness, no more
headaches, no more pains and trials that
our sons and daughter, our brothers and
sisters are facing right now, aba
father. But as we continue to live in
this world, aba father, help us to keep
our eyes focused upon the beautiful gold
heaven that you are going to prepare and
you will come back to bring us home and
we cannot wait, oh God. Yes, we are
living in the end time and we have we
need no glass to see that we're living
in the end time. This is the end time
that we're living in. Help us to keep
focus upon you as we continue to serve
you in spirit and in truth in the beauty
of your holiness. Thank you for today's
service and thank you for the rest
remaining of this beautiful, beautiful
time that we are here together. Let us
put on our spiritual muscles of faith.
Keep our lungs filled with divine oxygen
of grace by mindfully breathing in
prayer so that God will keep our lungs
filled with his mercy and fuel our soul
with agape love. Let us keep our eyes
focused upon the eastern sky that will
soon burst open and Jesus we will soon
see soon and very soon we will be home.
Until then let us continue to trust in
our Lord and Savior and let us continue
to dine in his word night and day as
Pastor Meyers come. Thank you God. Bless
him constantly. bless his studio once
more and bless everyone who are
participating in this beautiful
beautiful moment and this beautiful
breath of life in Jesus holy worthy and
precious name. Whatever I have faded a
fox of you this moment and behalf of
every individual fade it not to grant it
unto them but I pray God that you will
bind us up all with that cord of love
and that they love that we will never
depart from you these and other
wonderful mercies in Jesus holy worthy
and precious name I pray. Amen. And
amen.
When peace like a river
attendeth
my way.
When sorrows
like
billows.
Whatever
my Lord,
thou has taught me to say,
it is well with
my soul.
It is well. is well
with my soul.
It is well.
It is well with my soul.
My sin. Oh, the bliss of this glorious
thought.
My sin, not in part, but the whole
is nailed to the cross. And I
praise the Lord. Praise the Lord, oh my
soul. Oh my soul
for me is Christ be Christ has to live
in Jordan
above
me.
Oh trump of the angel
of voice of the Lord.
Blessed hope, blessed rest, oh my soul.
It is well.
It is well. It is well with my soul.
It is well
within my soul.
It is well.
It is well
with my soul.
The Lord is the day when my face shall
be sil
as a scroll.
The trump shall resound
and the Lord shall descend.
Praise
the Lord. It is well with my soul.
>> It is well.
>> It is well with my soul.
It is well
with my soul.
It is well.
It is well
with
my
soul.
With
my
Heat. Heat.
Heat.
Heat
up here.
Heat. Heat.
Amen. Church family. Amen. Happy
Sabbath. Um I want to welcome each of
you to the Living Matter online. Um 7th
Day Adventist Church. And today's
service you guys is um today's message
uh is going to be one that is
uh
straightforward.
and
to the point.
Um
you go ahead and put a one in the chat
and let me know that you're ready for
the word of God. Put that one in the
chat. Uh today, beloved, we are going to
be addressing the subject, the theme
that I've entitled the transchristian
movement. The transchristian
movement. I want you to pray with me.
Let's do that now. Heavenly Father,
please Lord speak to your people. Lord,
speak and may your voice be heard and
may be heard clearly is our prayer in
Jesus name. Amen.
Um,
what if I told you
that the Bible prophesied
a movement that would have
special significance,
especially in the last days, a movement
of trans Christians
Now, you may not understand what I mean
when I say transchristian.
You may have never heard that term
before. Um, but I would explain it as we
get into this message.
But in fact,
Paul along with others in the Bible
did prophesy
of a movement of trans Christians
at the end of time. I want to read to
you 2 Timothy chapter 3 beginning with
verse one. As I lay the foundation for
what trans Christianity is,
the Bible says this, know also that in
the last days perilous time shall come.
For men shall be lovers of their own
selves, covetous, boasters, proud,
blasphemers, disobedient to parents,
unthankful, unholy,
without natural affection, truce
breakers, false accusers, incontinent,
fierce, despisers of those that are
good, traitors, heady, high-minded,
lovers of pleasure,
more than lovers of God, having a form
of godliness,
but denying the power thereof.
From such, turn away.
Beloved, when I speak of the term
transchristian,
I'm speaking of a group of people who
profess
and on the outside have a form of
godliness
but deny the power thereof.
If I can
finish reading this verse, 2 Timothy
chapter 3:5.
In fact, um, let me just go ahead and
read the definition. The definition of
what a trans Christian is. A trans
Christian is one who selfidentifies
as a Christian despite not having been
born one.
You all
put a five in the chat just to help me
know that you understand what I mean
when I say a trans Christian.
I'll read the definition again.
A trans Christian is one who
self-identifies as a Christian despite
not having been born one.
and we're going to unpack the problem
with trans Christianity.
I said earlier that the Bible prophesied
at the end of time that there would be
such a movement. And I want to take you
to the book of Daniel
uh Daniel chapter 2 specifically which
also speaks of this movement. In Daniel
chapter 2, Nebuchadnezzar, the king of
Babylon has a dream in which God is
going to show him the future. And in
this dream, God shows him an image of a
man with head of gold, uh, a chest,
chest and arms of silver, belly and
thighs of brass, legs of iron, and then
toes of iron and clay. I see the
questions coming. Hold those questions
because I'm going to answer them.
uh Nebuchadnezzar does not know the
meaning of the dream and uh he he is
requesting someone to come forward and
to tell him the meaning of the dream.
Eventually Daniel the prophet is brought
to him and Daniel is going to break down
this dream for him. And I want you to
notice with me in Daniel chapter 2
beginning with verse 37 where Daniel
tells the king, "Thou o king
are the king of kings. For the God of
heaven has given thee a kingdom power
and strength and glory. And wheresoever
the children of men dwell, the beast of
the field, and the fowl of the heavens
has he given into thine hand, and has
made thee ruler over them all, thou art
this head of gold." Daniel tells
Nebuchadnezzar that king Babylon, the
king of Babylon, and thus Babylon itself
is the head of gold. Then he says,
"After thee shall arise another kingdom
inferior to thee, and another third
kingdom of brass, which shall bear rule
over all the earth. And the fourth
kingdom shall be strong as iron. For as
much as iron breakth in pieces, and
subdueth all these things, and as iron
breakth all these things, shall it break
and bruise in pieces.
Daniel is now breaking down the vision.
And in essence, what we come to
understand is not only did the head of
gold represent Babylon, but the chest
and the chest and arms of silver pointed
to Meo Persia, the belly and thighs of
brass pointed to the Grecian Empire, and
the legs of iron pointed to the Roman
Empire. And then I want you to notice
what Daniel 2:43 says. It says, "Whereas
thou sawest the iron mixed with miry
clay, they shall mingle themselves with
the seed of men, but they shall not
cleave one to another, even as iron is
not mixed with clay." So in this vision
after Nebuchadnezzar had seen the head
of gold and the chest and arms of silver
and the belly and thighs of brass and
the legs of iron the last thing he sees
are these toes 10 toes of iron and clay.
The iron and clay are mingled together.
And the and Daniel gives the
understanding that he simply says they
shall mingle themselves with the seed of
men. Now I want to break this down to
show you how we get to trans
Christianity.
You see the iron in the toes of iron and
clay would symbolize a continuation of
the of the Roman Empire, the political
system of the Roman Empire. But the
clay, this new element that is
introduced is significant. And here is
why. In Isaiah 64:8, the Bible says,
"But now, O Lord, you are our father. We
are the clay and you are our potter. We
are the work. We are all the work of
your hand. In the Bible, clay is
symbolic of God's professed people. But
we have a problem here in Daniel chapter
2. Because what the prophecy is showing
is that God's professed people are
mingling
with the politics of Rome.
And this is significant. Here is why.
Because at the end of this vision,
Nebuchadnezzar sees a stone cut out
without hands that hits the image. Not
in the head, not in the chest and arms
of silver, not in the belly and thighs
of brass, not in the legs of iron, but
in the toes of iron and clay. Why?
Because because in the toes of iron and
clay, you have a professed Christian
people
who have combined
or merged themselves
with the politics of this world with the
things of this world.
Thus, they are what we would call this
this iron and clay system is in essence
what we might call transch Christianity.
It looks like Christianity, but it
isn't. By the way, if we were to go back
to the book of Genesis chapter 6, it is
the first time we see something that is
similar to what we read in Daniel
chapter 2. the toes of iron and clay
mingling. The Bible says they will
mingle themselves with the seed of men.
When you go back to Genesis chapter 6,
the Bible describes in the days of Noah
that the sons of God saw the daughters
of men and went in unto them and chose
wives. So what the Bible is telling us
here, a lot of people think this is
talking about angels uh um uh uh having
uh intercourse with with with men, with
human beings, but this is not what the
Bible is saying at all. What the Bible
is is talking about here in Genesis
chapter 6 is simply that the sons of God
represented the lineage of Abel, the
lineage of of of of Seth, I'm sorry. And
and think of it in this way when Jesus
says in in in in the book of uh John as
many as received him to them gave you
power to become the sons of God. Sons of
God represent those that are supposed to
be converted while the daughters of men
would have represented the lineage of
Cain. And what's happening in Genesis
chapter 6 is that the line that is
supposed to be keeping themselves holy
have mingled themselves with the seed of
men. mingled themselves with an ungodly
lineage. And so what we find in Daniel
chapter 2 is a echo of the same thing.
It is Christians, professed Christians,
listen to me, professed Christians
mingling
with the things of this world, with the
kingdoms of this world. Now, I need you
to understand that this is Satan's MMO.
This is how Satan operates. You'll
remember in the garden in the in the
wilderness when Jesus is being tempted
in the wilderness in Matthew 4:8, the
Bible says again, "The devil taketh him
up into an exceeding high mountain and
showeth him all the kingdoms of the
world." All the kingdoms of the world.
All the kingdoms of the world. Remember
Daniel chapter 2, the toes of iron and
clay, the toes of iron
specifically represent the kingdoms of
the world, while the clay represents the
church, represents God's people. And in
Daniel 2, you have this mingling of
church and state. You have this mingling
of church and the world. And so when we
see here in Matthew chapter 4 that Satan
takes Jesus to an exceeding high
mountain and shows him all the kingdoms
of the world and the glory of them and
says and says all these things will I
give you if you will fall down and
worship me.
Please understand that the only way that
the clay gets intermingled with the iron
is through worshiping the enemy.
Y'all put a one in the chat if you
understand what I just said. The only
way that God's people begin to mingle
and blend with the world with the
kingdom with the with the kingdoms of
this world is they first must bow to
Satan's will in order to do this.
Genuine Christians
look a certain way.
Genuine Christians are a certain way.
Genuine Christians will not mingle with
the world.
Genuine Christians will not be of the
world. They will be in the world but not
of the world. And so today, beloved,
what I want to do is I want to share
with you six problems with the with the
transchristian community. Can I do that?
Six problems with the transchristian
community. Here is problem number one.
You don't get to redefine what a
Christian is.
TransChristians
for for a some strange reason cannot
define
what a Christian actually is.
If you go right now and ask a trans
Christian, what's a Christian? You might
get a a thousand different responses.
But beloved, listen to me. The actual
definition of a Christian is very
simple. It is one who follows Jesus.
Let me say it again. It is one who
follows and lives like Jesus.
Listen, listen, listen. You cannot be a
trans Christian and define Christian
other than what it is. Let me break it
down for you a little bit further. You
see, according to Philippians 2:5, the
Bible says, "Let this mind be in you
which was also in Christ Jesus."
A true Christian is going to have or is
going to exercise the mind of Christ. A
true Christian will not think like the
world. A true Christian will not react
like the world. A true Christian will
not endure or will not grab hold of the
things of the world mentally. A true
Christian thinks like Jesus and not like
the world. So listen carefully to me
then. If the mind of Christ is to love
your neighbor and you claim to be a
Christian but do not love your neighbor,
you are a trans Christian. You are part
of the trans Christian community.
Y'all put a one in the chat if you
understand what I'm saying.
You may call yourself Christian. You may
demand that others call you Christian.
But in reality, if you are not loving
your neighbor,
if you are not exercising the mind of
Christ,
which is demonstrated in love, you can
call yourself a Christian all day long
and demand that others call you
Christian. But I I have to be honest
with you.
You are not
a Christian.
I I I know that it is blunt and I know
that this message may be hard to hear,
but let me say it again. A Christian is
one who walks like Jesus. Let me show
you something. In Revelation 2:9,
the Bible says here, "I know thy works
and tribulation and poverty, but thou
art rich. And I know the blasphemy of
them which say they are Jews and are
not, but are of the synagogue of Satan."
Listen. So, in Revelation, there's a
group of people who who John says they
say they are this, but they're not.
They're demanding people say, "Hey, I'm
this." But they're not. Let me read it
again. Revelation chapter 3:9, "Behold,
I will make them of the synagogue of
Satan, which say they are Jews, and are
not,
but do lie. Behold, I will make them to
come and worship before thy feet, and to
know that I've loved thee." What is John
talking about here? What is John talking
about here? Let me break it down for
you. In the book of Romans chapter 2 28,
the New Testament says this, "For he is
not a Jew which is one outwardly,
neither is that circumcision which is
outward in the flesh. But he is a Jew
which is one inwardly, and circumcision
is that of the heart, in the spirit and
not in the letter, whose praise is not
of men, but of God." So according to the
New Testament, a Jew, a spiritual Jew
would be one who believes in Jesus and
follows Jesus. But John here is saying,
"Listen, I know that there are some out
there who are calling themselves
followers of God, Christians,
and yet are not." So they are actually
of the synagogue of Satan.
Beloved, this is a sobering thought.
It's a sobering thought. You see, Romans
12:2 tells us this. Be not conformed to
this world, but be ye transformed
by the renewing of your mind, that you
may prove what is that good and
acceptable and perfect will of God. True
transformation happens when your mind is
renewed. Therefore, beloved,
if
if you are if you claim to be a
Christian,
but you lack empathy,
compassion,
mercy,
grace,
if you lack the mind of Christ, if
you're fierce,
if you're proud,
please Understand
that you may demand all day long to be
called a Christian,
but the truth is
that is not the truth.
Be ye transformed by the renewing of
your mind. Which leads to the second
problem with the anti- with the I'm
sorry with the with the transchristian
community.
The second problem is this. You are what
you were assigned at birth. I'm sorry.
It's just the truth.
You are what you were assigned at birth.
Let me help you to understand because
you're like, "Pastor, what what are you
saying? How does this relate to trans
Christianity?" Well, let me show you.
According to John 3:3, the Bible says,
"Jesus answered and said unto him,
verily, verily, I say unto thee, except
a man be born again, he cannot see the
kingdom of God." Listen,
in order to be a Christian, you must be
born one.
And if you have not been born again, you
can claim all day long, I'm a Christian.
I'm a Christian. I'm a Christian. I'm a
Christian because I think I'm a
Christian. You can claim it all day
long. But I hate to tell you this. I
hate to be the bearer of bad news, but
I've got to be honest. You are not a
Christian.
If you have not been born again,
you cannot claim to be something which
you were not at your birth. Listen to
what John 1:12 says. But as many as
received him, to them gave he power to
become the sons of God, even to them
that believe on his name, which were
born not of blood, nor of the will of
flesh, nor of the will of man, but of
God.
Let me say it again. To be a Christian,
you must be assigned it at birth. Let me
break it down a little bit further for
you. Because you see, John 3:6 tells us,
"That which is born of the flesh is
flesh, and that which is born of the
spirit is spirit." You cannot be born of
the flesh and yet claim to be a
Christian, which is one that is born of
the spirit. So then, what I'm saying to
you, beloved, is very simple.
If you're born of the flesh, you can't
say, "I'm a Christian."
All of us are born of the flesh. But
then there are some who are born again
of the spirit. And if you are born again
of the spirit, then that makes you a
Christian at birth. You you there's no
changing that you you have been so from
birth. That is spiritual birth. However,
however, if you haven't been born again,
one of the evidences of which you don't
have the mind of Christ,
you don't have compassion, you don't
have empathy,
you put kingdom of this world over the
kingdom of God, whether it is good
kingdom of this world or bad kingdom of
this world, you put kingdom of this
world over the kingdom of God.
It is evidence
that your birth
your birth
reveals what you are.
That which is born of the flesh is
flesh. That which is born of the spirit
is spirit. And so respectfully, not in a
mean way, guys. Not in a mean way. I'm
not trying to be rude. I'm not trying to
be abrasive. I'm simply saying that if
you have not been born the thing, you
cannot be the thing.
If you have not been born again, you
cannot claim Christianity.
And you can get mad at me.
You can say, "I don't understand."
You know, you can you can do all the
things and I get it. I get it. I
understand. I I'm trying to be
compassionate about it. But but beloved,
truth is true. And we can't alter the
truth to fit
your concept of reality.
Are you understanding what I'm saying?
I mean, you can walk around and say to
yourself, "I'm a Christian all day long.
I'm a Christian. I'm a Christian. I'm a
Christian. But but the evidence that
that you that you that you the evidence
that you have no capacity, the evidence
that you hate others, the evidence uh
the the the fact that that
the fact that you live after the flesh
versus after the spirit
tells the reality
what is happening in today's Christian
community in America.
is a massive movement of trans
Christians.
TransChristians
who can who have this powerful way of
mingling light with darkness without
blinking an eye, without batting an eye.
this powerful way of of excusing and
explaining away evil
while also claiming
to be 100% Christian.
And and it is a stunning thing
to watch what would be otherwise
sensible people walking around saying
I'm a Christian when it is clear as day.
I mean, spiritual science doesn't lie.
Are y'all following me? Are y'all
catching what I'm saying?
You cannot bend the laws of spiritual
science and say, "I'm a Christian now
just cuz I want to say it. Just because
I have a position, just because I have a
position that that is wrong and that is
right, that makes me a Christian.
Beloved, righteousness is not by
position.
Righteousness
comes
by the death, burial, and resurrection
of Christ having a real life impact in
your life.
Christian biology cannot be ignored.
And then you you you know you the
transchristian community will just get
mad. How dare you say that I'm not what
I say I am.
How dare you say that that that that I'm
Come on. I I got to show you the next
point here. Point number three. Point
number three. The way you can tell an
actual Christian is that actual
Christians can reproduce.
Actual Christians
can reproduce.
Beloved, you may identify, you may
identify as Christian. I get it. I
understand.
But what is happening today in the
Christian world in America
is that thousands and thousands,
millions of people are are trans
Christians and don't even know it.
Beloved, I'm not saying that that
Christians don't make mistakes and
Christians don't have to repent of
certain things, but actual genuine
Christians actually repent of the stuff
that they do wrong when they do it
wrong. They recognize, "Yeah, that was
wrong. Man, I was weak in the flesh and
blah blah." They recognize, "Oh man,
that was the that was the enemy." They
they understand. They recognize. But
it's a totally different thing
to look evil in the eye and say, "Yeah,
that's good.
to watch evil unfolding and say, "Well,
I'm only concerned about certain types
of evil, but not other types of evil."
And this is what American Christianity
is doing today. It is it it is a system
that is based on trans Christianity. So,
pastor, what do you mean by an actual
Christian reproduces? Let me show you.
According to John 15:8, the Bible says
this, "Herein is my father glorified
that you bear much fruit, so shall you
be my disciples." Again, in verse 5,
just three verses up, I am the vine, you
are the branches. He that abideth in me,
and I in him, the same bringeth forth
much fruit, for without me you can do
nothing. So beloved, if you can't
reproduce, don't call yourself a
Christian.
Christians,
listen to me, Christians
spiritually, biologically
reproduce.
if you can't reproduce.
I mean, it
it is crazy that we're living in a day
and age where you have to tell someone
that if you're not able to produce,
how can you call yourself
a Christian? It almost feels like we're
living in an upside down world.
Look at what the Bible says. Look at
what the Bible says. Colossians 1:10,
that you may walk worthy of the Lord
unto all pleasing, being fruitful in
every good work and increasing in the
knowledge of God. And then there's
Galatians 5:22 and 23. But the fruit of
the spirit is love, joy, peace,
longsuffering, gentleness, goodness,
faith, meekness, temperance. Against
such there is no law. Beloved, listen to
me. If you are unable to produce,
you cannot call yourself a Christian
because a Christian is one who is able
to reproduce. Come, let me show you
Genesis 1 11. God said, "Let the earth
bring forth grass, the herb yielding
seed, and the fruit yielding a fruit
yielding and the fruit tree yielding
fruit after his kind, whose seed is in
itself upon the earth." And it was so I
need you to understand beloved
that that the evidence that you are a
Christian is that you can produce and
the thing that you produce the seed of
it is in itself the seed of it is in
itself. So, so as you're producing love,
in that love is more love seed,
joy, more joy seed. And listen, if you
say, "I'm a Christian," but you exhibit
the attributes that are against the Holy
Spirit, that are against the fruit of
the spirit. If you can actually rejoice
over the the fall of your enemies, if
you can actually in the name of Jesus
and in the name of America
rejoice over what you see as the fall or
defeat of your enemies
in the name of Jesus,
relishing
in pride pride and narcissism,
relishing in cruelty,
excusing away
in the name of honor not for God
but for some principle you hold.
Please understand
and please don't be offended
when the label transchristian
applies to you
because genuine Christians
produce the fruit of the spirit. They
are fertile.
And if you can't produce fruit, if
you're not producing fruit,
please understand.
I like the way it's put in the book
Reflecting Christ, page 341. It says
here, "The harvest is a reproduction of
the seed sown. Every seed yields fruit
after its kind. So it is with the traits
of character we cherish. Selfishness,
self-love, self-esteem, self-indulgence
reproduce themselves, and the end is
wretchedness and ruin.
Love, sympathy, and kindness yield
fruitage of blessing and a harvest that
is imperishable.
You want imperishable fruit,
beloved. If you are not producing the
fruit of the spirit,
you cannot go around demanding that
people call you a Christian.
Listen to this. In Matthew 7, Jesus's
own words. He says, "Beware of false
prophets which come to you in sheep's
clothing. Outward, outwardly I'm a
Christian, guys, but inwardly they are
ravening wolves. You shall know them by
their fruits. Do men gather grapes of
thorns or figs with thistles? Even so,
every good tree bringeth forth good
fruit, and a corrupt tree bringeth forth
evil fruit. A good tree cannot bring
forth evil fruit, neither can a corrupt
tree bring forth good fruit. Every tree
that bringeth not forth good fruit is
heuned down and cast into the fire.
Wherefore by their fruits you shall know
them. Not everyone that saith unto me,
Lord, Lord, shall enter the kingdom of
heaven, but he that doeth the will of my
father which is in heaven. Do you do you
understand this?
Just because you selfidentify
as a Christian
does not change the fact that you are
not bearing fruit. When you excuse
wicked fruit, when you justify wicked
fruit, when you cheer on wicked fruit,
when you see nothing wrong with wicked
fruit, certain wicked fruit, okay. Yeah,
because that wicked fruit. Yeah, I I can
I I can. But if you can't even identify
a wicked tree,
that is another sign.
You see, beloved, what is the will of
the father? Deuteronomy 5:29 says, "Oh,
that they had such a heart in them that
they would fear me always and keep all
my commandments that it might be well
with them and their children forever."
And you'll remember that Paul himself
says,
Paul himself says, I don't have I'm
sorry, it's not in my notes, but Romans
13:10, love workketh no ill to his
neighbor. Therefore, love is the
fulfilling of the law. Listen to me. Let
me say it again. If you are a Christian
that loves country over person, you may
call yourself a Christian,
but you're actually part of the trans
community.
You are.
I'm not trying to get you to be mad at
me.
All I'm saying is that
we need to be honest with reality, with
the truth.
Let me go to point four.
Point four. Your feelings don't change
biblical reality.
Your feelings don't change biblical
reality. You may feel
all day long that you're a Christian,
but the Bible tells us in Jeremiah 17:9,
Jeremiah 17:9,
that the heart is deceitful above all
things and desperately wicked.
So beloved, what you feel,
what you feel doesn't really amount to a
whole lot.
Please understand what I'm saying when I
when I when I'm trying to point out what
I'm trying to point out to you, beloved,
is that trans Christianity says, "Hey,
as long as I feel like I'm following
Jesus and and as long as I call myself a
a Christian, um, and as long as I have
certain positions uh that that the
Christian is supposed to have,
especially political ones, then that
makes me a Christian." But no, what that
makes you is a trans Christian. What
that makes you is part of the
transchristian community. And God,
it's not that God hates
trans-Christians.
I'm not saying that.
But God wants you to change your ways.
That's what he wants.
He wants you to change your ways. And
this is not coming from hate. It's
coming from love.
Now, I know that, you know, you may say,
"I want to be accepted." And I get that
God wants to accept you. But he's got to
accept you on biblical grounds. He can't
accept. He says, "Come to me the way you
are, but I'm going to change you so you
don't remain the same. So, you can't
hold on to your trans Christianity and
say, but but but you know, if I let this
go, then I won't have an identity." No.
God says, "Let this go and I will give
you a new identity. I will m I will make
you into a new person. I will grant you
a new birth."
Again, Jesus said in Matthew 7:21, "Not
everyone that saith unto me, Lord, Lord,
shall enter the kingdom of heaven, but
he that doeth the will of my father
which is in heaven." Many will say to me
in that day, Lord, Lord, have we not
prophesied in thy name? and in thy name
cast out devils, and in thy name done
many wonderful works. Then will I
profess unto them, I never knew you.
Depart from me, you trans Christian.
Depart from me, you that work iniquity.
Do you know how many people are walking
around right now just all in their
feelings? Yep. I'm a Christian. I'm a
Christian. But h
yes, I love when this happens. I put my
I put country over God. the the state of
Christianity in America today
is absolutely
it's almost like you think people are
losing their minds
because how can you walk around saying I
am a Christian and yet love the things
that are the furthest away from Jesus.
and cheer on the things that are the
furthest away from Jesus. How can you
do? How is it possible?
See, beloved, we can't depend on
feelings. Here's what we need to depend
on. Hebrews chapter 8:10 says this, "For
this is the covenant that I will make
with the house of Israel after those
days, sayeth the Lord. I will put my
laws into their minds and write them in
their hearts and I will be to them a god
and they shall be to me a people. You
can't trust your heart, your feelings.
You need to have the law of God written
on the heart. And if the law of God
is fulfilled in love, then beloved, it
is impossible
to hate any group of people. It is
impossible.
Listen to me y'all. It is impossible to
hate people or groups of people or think
yourself better than groups of people
while having the law of God written on
your heart. It just can't happen. It's
spirit. It's spiriologically
impossible.
Yeah, I just made the word up, but it
but I I'm making it a real word. It's
spiriologically
impossible.
You can't do that.
It's It's like saying a dog is a cat.
How do you say I'm a I'm a Christian and
yet hate groups of people? How do you
say I'm a Christian
and yet excuse evil?
Justify evil.
Rejoice
in evil. Rejoice in cruelty. Rejoice
in pride. Rejoice in in in in
narcissism. How do you do the how how is
that even possible? And beloved, we're
watching this form of Christianity so
that it reaches to such a high level in
America that it is at the highest levels
of our government.
When you can sit in a in a and watch a
national prayer breakfast in which is
like a which is like a twilight zone
and say this is Christianity.
How does that happen?
Let me get to point number five, y'all.
We're almost there. Point number five is
this. Cosmetic changes don't change who
you really are.
That's another problem with trans
Christianity. Cosmetic changes don't
change who you really are. So you can
you can try to go and get all kinds of
things done to change how you look on
the outside, but it doesn't change who
you really are.
It's it's it's really what 2 Timothy 3:5
is talking about
having a form of godliness.
A form of godliness meaning shape. I'm
trying to change how I look on the
outside. I'm trying to change my shape.
Having a form of godliness, but denying
the power thereof. And the text
literally says, "From such, turn away."
Wow.
From such, turn away. You may have the
shape of Christianity, but you lack the
power of it.
And so what ends up happening is that we
we try to go through all these these
changes like you know some kind of some
kind of spiritual surgery that says okay
I'mma take if I take these things it's
going to make me look more Christian.
But beloved you cannot you cannot be a
Christian from the outside to the end.
The only way it can happen is to be born
again. You cannot
by your own power,
by your own rules, by your own by your
own uh uh plans, by your saying, okay,
if I do this, this this this and this,
and if I believe this, this, this, and
this, then I look like a Christian. Ah,
see I used to look this way but now
listen you may look
listen
I got to admit
a a lot of the devil's spiritual surgery
is is stunning to behold. Like
you're looking at a wolf
but you think he's a sheep. Like that's
pretty good, y'all. That's pretty scary
when
you can't tell the difference. And I
think that's why Jesus put that parable
of the um the wheat and the tears.
Y'all remember the parable, the weed of
the tears?
We're like, "Yo, should we go when the
the you know the servants say to the
owner of the field, should we go and and
and and and pull out the tears?" And
it's like, don't do that because
you might end up uprooting some of the
wheat as you're doing this.
Yeah. Listen to me, you guys.
I I I admit
I admit that it's scary nowadays to like
you like you might think you're you
might think you're hanging out with a
Christian and next thing you know
the next thing you know
and so what I'm saying is
looking like a Christian on the outside
does not change who you and what you
really are on the inside.
Yes, the beacon network.
Having a form of godliness but denying
the power thereof. Listen, you know,
God's word, y'all, God's word is such a
joy.
It is because you get to tell people the
truth and
you get to do it in a way that hopefully
brings conviction and it is a beautiful
thing. It is a beautiful thing to watch
people go I get it. I get it. I see it
now. I understand.
So, so like Verette just said, if the
devil has the ability to change himself
into an angel of light,
then no wonder that he can also
transform his workers into the same.
And this is why we got to be so careful,
beloved, about
about understanding that there's a
difference between true Christianity
and trans Christianity.
True Christianity is real stuff.
TransChristianity is fake. And and for
the most part, you guys,
it's it's the it's the it's the rarity
that you couldn't tell.
But for the most part, you could be
like, "Yeah, I I heard you, but no, I'm
looking at you.
You're no." And it's not a matter of
judging, beloved. It's not like you're
saying you're not a No, no, no. It's not
a matter of judging. The Bible does say
that by their fruits you shall know
them. So if there is someone who is not
producing fruit or producing the wrong
kind of fruit, it's not judgment. It's
simply saying, "Oh, okay. I know what
you are." But now, if you turn around
and say, "No, I'm not that. I'm not that
tree. I am this tree."
Hey, how can a tree like this bear fruit
like that?
How can this good tree have as one of
its fruit lack of empathy? How can it
have narcissism? How can it have uh uh
um uh uh the spirit of revenge? How can
it have fierceness? How can how can the
tree you're saying you are produce these
fruits? That doesn't make spirit
biological sense.
Titus 1:16, they profess that they know
God, but in their works
deny him, being abominable and
disobedient, and unto every good work
reprobate.
Beloved,
this is this is serious stuff.
This is serious serious business, right?
Business right here.
God is trying to open the eyes of the
transchristian community before it is
too late.
Jesus described this very community when
he said in Matthew 15:8, "This people
draw nigh unto me with their mouth, lip
service,
lip service. And honorth me with their
lips, but their heart is far from me."
The only way, beloved, that we can
experience change is not cosmetically.
The Bible says, "Therefore, if any man
be in Christ, he is a new creature. Old
things are passed away. Behold, all
things are become new." That's what
we're after, beloved. That is what we're
after. And let me let me let me come to
this sixth point. Synthetic therapy
won't change you.
Synthetic
therapy will not change you. No amount
of external supplements, no amount of
what you try to do to maintain the
appearance that you are changed.
No, none of that will work.
And beloved, for a lot of us, the things
that we use to make ourselves look
Christian is our political position,
culture,
force.
We grab on to these things to say, see,
I'm Christian. See, I'm holy. What do
you mean you're holy? I'm holy. I have
this position about this cultural uh uh
uh you know issue and I have this
position about this cultural issue and I
believe that this is the way that things
should be done in this country
politically speaking and therefore I am
Christian
and we think that these that these
positions that we hold is what makes us
look Christian beloved. But may I
suggest to you, may I suggest you that
the Bible says in Jeremiah 17:5, "Cursed
be the man that trusteth in man, and
maketh flesh his arm, whose heart
departeth from the Lord." When you trust
in man,
when you believe that men
and sometimes ungodly men
is the way for you to put your tr I'm
putting my trust in the because it says
Christianity.
Beloved, listen to me.
Cultural Christianity is trans
Christianity.
It is I like that Clint. It is cult
And what we need to understand is very
simple.
It is not the synthetic stuff.
It is not the synthetic stuff, y'all,
that makes us into new creatures. Listen
to what the Bible says in Zechariah 4:6.
The Bible says, "He answered me and
said, this is the word of the Lord unto
Zerubbabel, saying, not by might, nor by
power, but by my spirit, sayeth the Lord
of hosts." Do you know that? Do you know
that um the trans-Christian community
probably hates this verse? They claim
the verse, but what they really mean is
by might and by power. Oh, yeah. Also by
your spirit. It can't work like that.
The trans-Christian community when we go
back to Daniel chapter 2 is a community
of people that have idolized country
here in America have idolized country
over God.
And beloved, it is at a level right now
that
that is absolutely stunning to behold.
We're almost done. We're almost there.
This is my final point. Real love
doesn't lie to people about their
spiritual condition.
Yep.
Real love does not lie to people about
their spiritual condition.
If you have a friend or a loved one
who you know
says, "Uh,
yeah,
I'm a Christian."
And yet you understand, you see clearly
um
the fruit is not there.
I'm not I'm not saying to judge that
person, but what I'm saying is don't
don't bow to the false image.
Pray for that person. You don't have to
be rude. You don't have to be mean. You
don't have to tell the people you're
you're not a you're you're not a
Christian.
But you pray for that person and you do
your best to help that person see
that to be a Christian literally means
to be like Jesus.
And if Jesus were here today, I will
tell you, do you know how many
Christians would hate Jesus?
If Jesus were were in some, you know,
strange way to be present on earth right
now, the real Jesus,
do you know how many Christians would be
like, "No, thank you.
This is not the picture of Jesus that we
want. And I you're not down with the
stuff we're down with. And so nah, we
got our Jesus.
We have our Cyrus.
We have our Caesar.
The Christian world today would hate
Jesus for what he stood for what he
would stand for.
They would rather a barabus
than Jesus.
And so real love doesn't lie. This is
why God says in Revelation 13 3:19, "As
many as I love, I rebuke and chasten. Be
zealous, therefore, and repent." Yeah.
Yeah.
Acts 18 tells us, "But you shall receive
power after the Holy Ghost has come upon
you." That's what God wants for us. He
wants us to be able to get that power,
that dunamis, that dynamis. He wants us
to be able to understand that when we're
born again, the things that we thought
we would never be able to do, the things
that that that we're like, I God says,
I'mma give you power to love. That's
what the power is for.
Power to love.
Power to walk like Jesus, to be like
Jesus. So again, Proverbs 27:5 and 6
tells us, "Open rebuke is better than
secret love. Faithful are the wounds of
a friend, but the kisses of an enemy are
deceitful.
I think about Daniel chapter 2, where
after Nebuchadnezzar had been told about
this dream, head of gold, chest and arms
of silver, belly and thighs of brass,
legs of iron, toes of iron and clay,
that in the very next chapter, in the
very next chapter, Nebuchadnezzar goes
and makes an image of all gold.
He sees himself as who he wants to see
himself as.
All gold. I'm good. This is the reality
of my kingdom. Not what you told me over
there in Daniel 2. This is the reality
of my kingdom. And then he wanted them
to bow down to his reality.
Hey, my truth is different from your
truth.
And he wanted the people to bow down.
And everybody did bow down except the
three faithful people that were there,
Shadrach, Meshach, and Abednego. They
were like, "Listen, man. We we can't
it's not that we, you know, it's not
that we're trying to disrespect you
unnecessarily.
Um,
but we can't bow down to your
ideas of truth,
your idea of reality when this is not
the reality.
And beloved, that's how we need to stand
today.
I know I know you might risk, you know,
offending the transchristian community
and they might be very upset with you
and I get it.
I understand.
But the truth is the truth. We've got to
learn to speak the truth in love. We've
got to learn to speak the truth, to pray
the truth, and to come close to these
people. You know, I'm not saying run
away from them or you're strange. No,
no, no. I mean,
God calls us to draw close
because he loves everybody, y'all.
He loves everybody
from the from the best of us to the
worst of us. He loves us all. And
ultimately, you guys, he wants to see us
all saved. You understand?
So while they may not understand and
while they may be offended and you know
you won't call me by my by my what I
identify as
you won't acknowledge that I'm a true
Christian.
Why not?
It's not about the individual you guys.
It's about the movement. And the
movement has gotten into people's minds
and told them and corrupted them to
think you can be a Christian just by
claiming the name Jesus. That's all. If
you claim the name Jesus, you can be you
can be as mean, vindictive, you can be
as whatever you want and and you can
say, "Hey, this is the Christian way."
And and and it just doesn't matter
because as long as you say, "I'm a
Christian." Then anything you do or say
goes.
So it's time to be born again.
That's the conclusion.
Take that person
by the hand and and and and talk with
them and pray with them.
and show them
in the Bible this is what it means to be
a Christian
and then invite them to actually follow
Jesus.
You can be born again. It is a miracle
but it is a real thing. You can be born
again. God can convert you. It is it is
God's conversion therapy.
And the Holy Spirit works out this
conversion therapy to help you move from
from a heart that is waxing cold to a
heart that is on fire. From a heart that
rejoices in in in in uh in false
Christianity.
from a heart that says that a deceptive
heart that says, "Hey, as long as long
as I have these positions, I'm I'm I'm
good.
I check the Christian the the Christian
box." Yep. Check, check, check. I'm a
Christian. And and the the evil people
over there are the bad guys.
I know the world says a lot about
conversion therapy these days, but I'll
tell you what, I believe that God's
conversion therapy can change any trans
Christian into a true Christian. If you
believe that, put a one in the chat.
We're going to close in prayer. Um,
beloved, I pray um, and I want you to
understand this message has come from a
place of love and and I want you to
know, trans Christian community, I love
you.
I love you. I love you. I love you. And
God loves you. And God wants to see you
really stand up and be a light in the
world. And you can do that. Just give
your give your heart to Jesus and have
him transform it and you will be able to
bear fruit. It is possible. You will be
able to bear fruit. You can change on
the inside. You can literally become
a genuine Christian. And that doesn't
mean one that doesn't make mistakes, but
it means one who understands that this
is what it means to follow Jesus. and
doing this is not following Jesus.
I see the one in the chat. I'm going to
pray and then we're going to close out.
Heavenly Father, I want to thank you,
Lord, for
this message.
That is an appeal to the trans Christian
community,
Lord. That they will understand that the
damage they are doing to your name,
claiming Christianity while having the
spirit of the enemy, the spirit of the
world, the spirit of of fierceness and
of and of politics and the spirit of of
vengeance and the spirit of narcissism.
All of these things, Lord, in the name
of Christianity, it is driving
millions of people around the world away
from the gospel
because people are seeing the hypocrisy.
Please Lord,
please I pray that you would do
something mighty in this trans-Christian
community and help them Lord to come out
of Babylon. That's what your word says
because Babylon represents confusion and
there is so much confusion out there
that people are now confused about what
it means to actually be a Christian. So
Lord, call the transch Christian
community out. May they hear the truth.
May they undergo your conversion
therapy. May they be able to be changed
so that they can produce fruit. And
Lord,
show them that they can be Christians,
not just in form without power,
but actually in the power of the Holy
Spirit changing their inward sides.
Thank you, Lord. Thank you for hearing
and answering this prayer because we ask
it in the precious and holy name of
Jesus. Amen. And amen.
Guys, thank you for listening um uh to
the message today. I I want to just put
up the final uh slide here that will let
you know here is how you can uh get in
touch with us for those of you who want
to uh connect uh on the uh afterlow. Uh
we'll put that link in the chat. Uh you
can see where you can follow us on
social media. You can connect with uh
LOC. you can put your prayer requests um
submit your prayer requests as well. And
for those of you who who want to get
into Bible study classes to study for
baptism purposes, uh there is the email
bibleworker living.urch.
Please reach out to us and uh we would
love to walk you through the process of
being baptized or even rebaptized.
maybe being baptized for the first time,
studying this message and understanding
uh the Bible in all its fullness and
glory. And so again, that's how you can
reach out and connect with us. And may
God bless you. Uh may God keep you and
we will see uh some of you. By the way,
all of you are invited to the um to the
afterlow. Uh the link is in the chat. So
please feel free to jump on join us and
may God bless you and keep you. Amen.
Thank you for joining us today. If this
is your first time worshiping with us,
please check out our website at living
manana.urch. We are not just here for
Sabbath service. We have weekly
programming too that covers mental
health, physical health, weekly prayer
service, financial health, and proving
the existence of God. It is our desire
that our programming will continue to
bless you. Please continue to pray for
us as we fulfill God's mission to go
into all the world with the gospel of
Jesus Christ.